<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/rss2full.xsl"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Scoutmob San Francisco</title>
    <description>Mobile Deals + Curious Finds</description>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/scoutmob/sf" /><feedburner:info uri="scoutmob/sf" /><atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" /><feedburner:browserFriendly></feedburner:browserFriendly><item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1697</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1697</guid>
      <title>50% off The Bagelry</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1697/original.jpg?1321474632" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; There’s no question about what you’ll find inside The San Francisco Bagelry. Not only is their livelihood boldly presented in the business’ name, there’s a bagel hanging on the storefront that could be spotted from the top of Coit Tower, &lt;a href="http://www.somethingawful.com/d/photoshop-phriday/birds-human-hands.php" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;if you were a bird at least&lt;/a&gt;. But when you know how to do bagels up right like these guys do, you let the world know. While a lot of “the other guys” are busy steaming their bagels, the crew at The Bagelry is doing everything by hand, the old fashioned way, to produce chewy, New York style bagels. What you’ll find in the display cases here are dense, boiled bagels, not the flimsy bread dough types you’ve probably suffered through before. No bagel is complete without a good &lt;i&gt;schmear&lt;/i&gt; of cream cheese, which The Bagelry makes from scratch, as evidenced by the rows of plastic containers topped with little shavings of fresh produce like veggies, chives and strawberries. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

On weekdays, bagels come rolling out of the bagel machine in the back until about 9:30 a.m., while weekends require two baking sessions due to demand, and a line that’s consistently out the door. Check out the Really Seedy bagel, topped with sesame and poppy seeds, onion, garlic and a touch of salt. And if you can’t choose between all the scrumptious flavors, don’t worry, you can take these babies home by the dozens, too. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
One Dozen Bagels, $10.75&lt;br&gt;
Peanut Butter &amp; Bananas Bagel, $2.50&lt;br&gt;
Lox &amp; Cream Cheese, $6.75&lt;br&gt;
Egg, Sausage, Cheese Breakfast Bagel Sandwich, $5&lt;br&gt;
Egg &amp; Bacon Breakfast Bagel Sandwich, $4&lt;br&gt;
Roast Turkey Bagel Sandwich, $6&lt;br&gt;
Pastrami Bagel Sandwich, $6&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Friday, 6:30 a.m. to 2:30 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday – Sunday, 7 a.m. to 2:30 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-21 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Fri, 18 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>The Bagelry</location>
      <address>2139 Polk St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94109</zip>
      <latitude>37.7965</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.422</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 441-3003</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1697/original.jpg?1321474632</image>
      <website>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-bagelry-san-francisco</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2669</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2669</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do This Weekend, November 18-20</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2669/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1321559157" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We’ve been getting second and third helpings at meals lately in preparation for Thanksgiving. The more we stretch our stomach out now, the more pieces of turkey and pie we can pack in there on the big day. But, in between training for the upcoming holiday, you can bet your britches we’ll be hanging out here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

THREAD: INDIE DESIGN &amp; FASHION AT THE METREON&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, November 20, 11 a.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Holiday shopping. Either you can prepare yourself to hear that phrase about a gazmillion times over the next few months, or you can get it over with now and put your earmuffs on the next time the subject comes up. Thread Show is a traveling showcase of top notch indie fashion. Shopping is just the beginning of what’s going down at this event. They’ve got live music, an art gallery, nail bar, wellness lounge, gift wrapping and more, if you can even believe that. &lt;a href="http://threadshow.com/show_info.php?show_id=125&amp;show=rsvp" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Pre-register&lt;/a&gt; to get in for $5 or donate clothes at the door for $5 entry. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://threadshow.com/show_info.php?show_id=125" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Thread in SF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1566" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;L'acajou Bakery &amp; Café&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

CARY LANE’S IN-STORE BIRTHDAY PARTY &lt;br&gt; &lt;i&gt;Friday, November 18, 8 p.m to 11 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The birthday celebration continues at clothier Cary Lane, who celebrates three years in business with food from &lt;a href="http://www.lavictoriabakery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;La Victoria Bakery&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://patxispizza.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Patxi’s Pizza&lt;/a&gt; and sips from Magners Cider, Svedka Vodka, Red Bull and Fuze. And, everything in the store will be an additional 30% off.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/carylane" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Cary Lane&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1560" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;The Sage Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

A WAKE FOR 1978 AT DOUBLE PLAY BAR&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday, November 18, 7 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1978 in San Francisco was one tough year. Jim Jones and the Peoples Temple (which started in SF) wiped out 918 people and Harvey Milk and George Moscone were assassinated. Tonight, Mike Weiss shares his new film, &lt;i&gt;Double Play: The Hidden Passions Behind the Double Assassination of George Moscone and Harvey Milk &lt;/i&gt;, Jack Hirschman will read his poem &lt;i&gt;The Jonestown Arcane&lt;/i&gt; along with a few other sharings of accounts of the zeitgeist at the time. It’s being held at Double Play bar, because you’re going to need a drink or ten during the course of this history lesson.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.citylights.com/info/?fa=event&amp;event_id=1380" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;City Lights Books&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1671" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Free chicken burrito at El Metate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2654</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2654</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Caption This! Friday Photo Fun</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2654/BigThumb2.jpg?1321559938" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Give us your best witty caption to go with this extra curious pic on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

We'll post some our favorites to this here website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

As for this interesting image from last week, here are some of the caption contributions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src=" http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/seen/2613/captionthis.jpg?1320940119"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR FAVORITE:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The medical bills are bad enough, but now she's gonna need therapy too."&lt;br&gt;
- Laura Rice Heath

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;HONORABLE MENTIONS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"SPACE JAM"&lt;br&gt;
- Pablo Gnecco&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I should be up front and honest with you, this is just a one night stand."&lt;br&gt;
- Richard Bakare&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

‎"Pretty sure this is what Billy meant by robotripping."&lt;br&gt;
- Ilana Wolk&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The rabbit was horrified to find that his daughter was not lying and that a large child was indeed coming out of the closet and tormenting his little one at night."&lt;br&gt;
- Juan Jose Ramirez&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Morphine, it makes ordinary situations extraordinary."&lt;br&gt;
- James Williams&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

‎"If you can see me it means the drugs are working, Sarah."&lt;br&gt;
- Laura Sjogren&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"On second thought, maybe she was too young to see Donnie Darko."&lt;br&gt;
- Lauren McCain Earley&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Everyone loves the soothing sensation of Vicks® Vap-O-Rub."&lt;br&gt;
- Kat Gilpatrick</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2654/BW2.jpg?1316724954</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2676</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2676</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>The Potrero Hill Kid: Troublemaking in the 1950s</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sf_bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2676/SF_bigthumb2.jpg?1321298071" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Growing up here in the city these days, you can get in to a lot of trouble. But for Mike Bradbury and his “&lt;a href="http://www.mountainhomenews.com/blogs/1582/entry/38412" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;hooligan friends&lt;/a&gt;,” trouble in the 1950s meant rolling tires down hills straight in to traffic, turning straws in to spitball guns and stealing candy bars and hubcaps. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/potrero_bradbury.jpg" alt="Potrero Kid Bradbury Picture" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Mike says if your family didn’t make that much money, you could live on a street like Rhode Island. His family lived in the "slum section" of Pennsylvania Avenue, but his dad always paid the extra five bucks to get a space in the garage (that’ll get you, what, about 45 minutes at a meter these days?).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/potrero_house.jpg" alt="Potrero Kid House Picture" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

He used to go “shopping” (candy bar stealing) at the Hilltop Grocery, which still stands in some form today. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/potrero_grocery.jpg" alt="Potrero Kid Grocery Picture" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.mountainhomenews.com/blogs/1582/entry/44639/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Check out his full blog post&lt;/a&gt; for more old-timey photos and to find out where his bad kid ways eventually lead him. 
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1695</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1695</guid>
      <title>50% off The Chameleon Café</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1695/original.jpg?1321396774" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; His name was Buster, and more times than not, &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KMT1FLzEn9I" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;he was hard to find&lt;/a&gt;. But that trait wasn’t why owner Melody named her Nob Hill café after her beloved pet. She simply set out to establish an ever-changing space that could adapt to the community it catered to. And at this sunny, spacious spot you’ll find what feels like an extension of a cozy living room: durable naval chairs surrounding substantial tables, a bookshelf of “borrowable” books, a stack of board games and plenty of neighborhood chatter. Over the past seven years, staff and regular patrons have gotten to know each other, so when one guy comes in for his morning coffee, Melody welcomes him back from a long trip to Israel while she pours his drink. Alongside caffeine rich options, you’ll find café fixtures like the popular breakfast bagel stuffed with ham, egg and cheese, a variety of salads and six sandwich choices, including a sunflower chicken salad sandwich. On the whiteboard, you’ll find organic specials like turkey cranberry and Italian combo paninis and empanadas stuffed with grilled chicken and jack cheese or spinach, artichoke and chard, with a side of chimichurri sauce – garlic, olive oil, parsley and spices. On Thursdays, the Mexican menu is extended further when street food favorite &lt;a href="http://www.eltonayense.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;El Tonayense&lt;/a&gt; rolls up. Enjoy an al pastor taco alongside one of Chameleon’s craft beers or local wines. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Buster may be hiding for good, but we guarantee you’ll find yourself at The Chameleon.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Almond Joy – chocolate, espresso, almond, steamed milk, whipped cream, $3.50&lt;br&gt;
Fresh Baked Pastries from &lt;a href="http://batterbakery.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Batter Bakery&lt;/a&gt;, $2.50&lt;br&gt;
Fruit Parfait, $5.95&lt;br&gt;
Ham &amp; Brie Sandwich, $6.50&lt;br&gt;
Smoked Salmon Salad, $7.95&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Wednesday, 7 a.m. to 3 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Thursday &amp; Friday, 7 a.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday &amp; Sunday, 8 a.m. to 8 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-18 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Thu, 17 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>The Chameleon Café</location>
      <address>1299 Pacific Ave</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94109</zip>
      <latitude>37.7957</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.417</longitude>
      <phone>415-351-0338</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1695/original.jpg?1321396774</image>
      <website>http://www.yelp.com/biz/the-chameleon-cafe-san-francisco</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2679</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2679</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Let Someone Else Do The Cooking</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sf_bigthumb1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2679/SF_bigthumb1.jpg?1321299337" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Your new favorite brunch, breakfast, lunch, dinner, meals-on-the-go, warm-from-the-oven-treats, evening hang out spot is set to open on December 4th. Alison Clement of &lt;a href="http://squaremealssf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Square Meals&lt;/a&gt; and Jen Musty of &lt;a href="http://batterbakery.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Batter Bakery&lt;/a&gt; are taking over 2127 Polk Street with their new joint concept. Alison whips up healthy meals that can be enjoyed in the restaurant as easily as they can be taken home, and Jen provides sweet and savory goodies to complement, like Sweet Potato Goat Cheese Rosemary Scones and Pumpkin Cinnamon Cream Cheese Cupcakes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: So Jen, where did you learn to make all your delicious goodies?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
JEN: I am a mom-taught and self-taught baker. I grew up baking, my mom says, from the point that I could stand on a chair next to her. Throughout high school and college, I would always bake if I was bored or stressed out. After college is when I really started tinkering with recipes. I went to school for business and got an accounting degree and started a job in public accounting, but I would sit there at my desk every day thinking &lt;i&gt;What am I going to make when I get home tonight?&lt;/i&gt; I started out doing some catering for small business, and it just kind of snowballed from there. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: You make so many &lt;a href="http://batterbakery.com/menus_dessert.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;different yummy treats&lt;/a&gt;, is there one thing you especially look forward to making? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
JEN: The Fall treats are some that are very memorable for me. The pumpkin bread recipe is something I grew up with. Every October 1st, my mom would make the first batch of pumpkin bread. Gingerbread and applesauce spice muffins, I was eating from the time I was two years old. I’ll open the oven and smell them baking and get transported back to the time I was little.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Yum! Ok, Alison, what was your inspiration for taking healthy food and sticking it in the on-the-go world?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ALISON: When I started cooking, I was a personal chef, so I was already a part of solving the problem of how busy people with young kids can eat a well-rounded diet and fresh foods. It was frustrating to me, though, because it was a high price point, and people had to commit ahead of time to many meals per week. So I kind of backed in to the prepared meals on the go, and for the past three years since I've been working out of a commercial kitchen, you can &lt;a href="http://gomobo.com/Order/Order.aspx?VendorId=2381" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;order meals online&lt;/a&gt; and have them delivered. With that, you still need to order 24 hours in advance, though. The new store is the solution to that. It’s not a competition to restaurants, it’s another avenue for eating. I’m also kind of old fashioned, and I think it’s really important to sit down and eat dinner as a family. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Tell us more about the new space:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ALISON: We’re taking the burden off customers, so when you come in, you’ll be able to buy a roasted chicken and a side dish and cupcakes to take home, but only have one credit card to swipe. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: How often will the menu change?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ALISON: It will change all the time; we’re not having anything printed that says what we cook. We have two options: you can get the prepared meals that come as a package, or you can mix and match. As a blog post, we’ll announce the main entrées we’ll be cooking for that month, and then the side dishes will always change.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: With your beer and wine license, you’re creating a night time hangout, too...&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
JEN: We want to offer the space as an alternative to a bar. People are out and about non-stop on Polk Street, but we want to create a spot where you can come in and grab a dessert and a wine pairing or a tapas snack and a beer without getting elbowed and jostled in a crowded bar.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: What did we miss?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
JEN AND ALISON: Drop in during our opening on December 4th. We're going to have lots of fun stuff going on. It'll probably be more like a party all week, actually.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;i&gt;Leave the Thanksgiving cooking to Chefs Alison and Jen. Check their scrumptious, festive offerings below. Email &lt;a href="mailto:ChefAlison@SquareMealsSF.com?subject=Me Want Thanksgiving Feast! (via Scoutmob)" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Email Chef Alison&lt;/a&gt; or give her a call at 415-552-3501. &lt;a href="mailto:info@batterbakery.com?subject=Me Want Thanksgiving Treats (via Scoutmob)" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Email Jen&lt;/a&gt; or call 415-994-4944. Orders can be placed and delivered together.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/thanksgiving_menu.jpg" alt="Thanksgiving Menu Square Meal SF" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/gobbleup.jpg" alt="Batter Bakery Menu" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2668</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2668</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>A Hidden Bomb Shelter Trapped In Time</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2668/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1321381546" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Our beautiful little bay has been the site of many military defenses and fortifications since the Civil War, but it was during the Cold War that we began burrowing deep inside the earth in the event of a nuclear attack. Photographer Mike Hows, of the site &lt;a href="http://takenpictures.com" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;TakenPictures&lt;/a&gt;, delved deep in to one of the U.S. Navy’s San Francisco nuclear fallout shelters to get a look at what subterranean life was like back in 50s and 60s. It’s a glimpse in to a space where time seems to stand still. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Among dusty desks in the command center, canned emergency drinking water and an instant toilet for 50 people, he also captured disaster control plans and ghostly hospital beds. 

&lt;a href="http://takenpictures.com" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Click over to his site&lt;/a&gt; to check out the full set. </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2650</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2650</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Win A Prize If You Recognize</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2650/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1321381869" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;How well do you know your city? Give us your best guess on this mystery location and we'll send a sweet, sweet prize to one lucky winner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Reply to the Scoutmob daily email with your answer, or hit us up through &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/scoutmob" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.scoutmob.com/images/scoutmob_images/other_images/recognizedline.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2608/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320773359"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


Last week’s answer: Riptide Bar&lt;br&gt;
Last week's winner: Thomas Carroll</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2650/SM_home_Contentimage2.jpg?1316545886</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1671</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1671</guid>
      <title>100% off El Metate</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1671/original.jpg?1320957216" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; El metate, besides being really fun to say, is an Aztec word for the stone tools used to ground corn in to tortilla appropriate powder. Here at 22nd and Bryant, El Metate means delicious Mexican food brought all the way from the heart of Mexico by owner Francisco. As a child, he spend countless hours with his grandmother in her kitchen in Guanajuato, learning how to marinate chicken, fry pinto beans in whole black pepper and corn oil for an amazing flavor profile, and come up with a sauce he uses on his fish tacos &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VuE_jqYNi3c" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;that’s so secret&lt;/a&gt;, the only ingredient information he’s willing to give up is “spices.” The secret sauce is only part of what makes the fish tacos so memorable, though. Each piece of fish comes covered in a crispy batter that’s strictly breadcrumbs, no egg or flour. It’s an original recipe Francisco introduced about seven years ago, and continues to be on the top of everyone’s favorite list. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Also on that list is El Metate’s chicken burrito. There are many ways to make a chicken burrito, but the El Metate way involves juicy thigh meat, fried pinto beans and jasmine rice, which Francisco says is more flavorful than other rices. The heat level is left up to you, with a few sections of the walls devoted to a spicy rack, not a spice rack, filled with every taste bud riling hot sauce you can imagine. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Chicken Burrito, $5.50 (free with deal!)&lt;br&gt;
Fish Taco, $2.75&lt;br&gt;
Quesadilla, $6&lt;br&gt;
Torta, $6.25&lt;br&gt;
Chicken Tortilla Soup (large), $5&lt;br&gt;
Pork Tamale w/ chile verde sauce platter, $7.75&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Daily, 10 a.m. to 10 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-17 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2011 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>100%</percentageOff>
      <location>El Metate</location>
      <address>2406 Bryant St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94110</zip>
      <latitude>37.7557</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.41</longitude>
      <phone>415-641-7209</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1671/original.jpg?1320957216</image>
      <website>http://elmetate.webs.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2642</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2642</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>The Craftiest of Locally Crafted Brews</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2642/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1321308444" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Mmmm. Beer. It does a body good. Ok, maybe not so much, but it’s delicious and makes us feel happy, so that’s good enough. Why go for some generic can of Brand X Light when you sip on brews made here in our own backyard? Last week we asked you: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WHO MAKES THE CRAFTIEST OF LOCALLY CRAFTED BREWS?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR SCOUT SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; There are a lot of talented brewers in the city, but the fact that Patrick and Bryan consistently brewed up tasty unique beers in a garage in SoMa puts &lt;a href="http://pacbrewlab.blogspot.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Pac Brew Lab&lt;/a&gt; at the top of my locally crafted beer list. And when I &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2177" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;got to sit down with them&lt;/a&gt; over one of their delicious Imperial Stouts, well, let’s just say it sent my heart and taste buds aflutter. They recently &lt;a href="http://www.livesoma.com/2011/11/02/pac-brew-lab-soma/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;held their last free brew night&lt;/a&gt; in order to move the operation to &lt;a href="http://www.devilscanyonbrewery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Devil’s Canyon Brewery&lt;/a&gt; in Belmont, but every sip of a Pac Brew Labs creation will always bring me back to the good old garage days. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;YOU SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I really like &lt;a href="http://21st-amendment.com/" target="_blank"&gt;21st Amendment&lt;/a&gt;, but only for their seasonal brews. I'm gonna have to go old school on this one and say &lt;a href="http://anchorbrewing.com/beers/" target="_blank"&gt;Anchor Steam&lt;/a&gt; still takes the cake. I also like &lt;a href="http://www.triplevoodoobrewing.com/TripleVoodoo/faces/Home.xhtml" target="_blank"&gt;Triple Voodoo&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;br&gt;
- Jessica Copi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"In San Francisco? I'll say &lt;a href="http://www.almanacbeer.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Almanac&lt;/a&gt;. In the greater Bay Area? &lt;a href="http://www.drinkdrakes.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Drake's&lt;/a&gt; in San Leandro."&lt;br&gt;
- George Georgerson&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://thirstybear.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Thirsty Bear&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.magnoliapub.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Magnolia&lt;/a&gt; quench a thirst pretty nicely."&lt;br&gt;
- Lance Walker&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://socialkitchenandbrewery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Social Kitchen &amp; Brewery&lt;/a&gt;!"&lt;br&gt;
- Megan Allison Wade&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;NEXT WEEK’S WHAT SAY YOU: WHERE DO YOU GO FOR LIP-SMACKING CLAM CHOWDER?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Oh clam chowder, you warm us heart and soul. Where do you go to load up on one of the heartiest soups on the (fish) market? Hit us up on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2655</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2655</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Matt Fleming Cranks Out Some Art</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2655/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1321306544" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;When we attended &lt;a href="http://artcrank.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Artcrank&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href="http://www.111minnagallery.com/" target="_blank"&gt;111 Minna&lt;/a&gt; awhile back, there were lots of cool, bike themed posters to check out, but there was one burst of hot pink awesomeness that really caught our eye. 

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/matt1.jpg" alt="Matt Fleming Art" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

The artist is &lt;a href="http://www.blackt-shirt.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Matt Fleming&lt;/a&gt;, who says he got in to biking when he moved to the Bay Area and realized he could survive without the stress of owning a car. When his dad gave him a Specialized Roubaix, riding became an even bigger part of his life. Here, he tells us about is unusual source of design inspiration and sketches out his own version of “Scoutmob:”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: What did your earliest art look like?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
MATT: It was some strange stuff. The earliest recollection I have is something that looks like an old jukebox with zigzag borders radiating around it. When I started to draw heavily in third grade, it was a lot of "tough guys" like super heroes or ninjas.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: You have a ton of tees in your store. How often do you add new designs?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
MATT: &lt;a href="http://shop.kindredmarket.com/collections/black-t-shirt" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;The storefront&lt;/a&gt; is a nice outlet for me to crank out random design ideas, but that only happens when I have a little breathing room between client work. It's an ongoing side project I’d like to eventually update quarterly to keep interest, and there's quite a long list of ideas waiting for my attention.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  Your poster really caught our eye at Artcrank. What was going through your head when you put this bad boy together?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
MATT: Thank you! Artcrank has become one of the few projects each year that is dictated 100% by me, and there are no compromises made due to input from other parties. When that's the case, I actually have a difficult time deciding what it is I want to focus on, so I resolved to mix together nearly all the ideas I had. Initially, each one of the little vignettes was a skeleton of a poster idea that I couldn't let go. The overall theme is my progression from using a bike for transportation to riding out of pure joy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Please doodle us your idea of what a “Scoutmob” is: &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/matt2.jpg" alt="Matt Fleming Art" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Oooooh we like! Ok, you design a lot of band merch (not to mention your &lt;a href="http://www.thebaybridged.com/2009/09/01/our-new-artist-in-residence-matthew-fleming/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;artist in residency with The Bay Bridged&lt;/a&gt; awhile back). What local bands are playing through your speakers currently?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
MATT: &lt;a href="http://www.bhibhiman.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Bhi Bhiman&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.liarose.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Lia Rose&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://mattnathanson.com/modernlove/" target="_blank"&gt;Matt Nathanson&lt;/a&gt;, all in the singer/songwriter genre, and my friends &lt;a href="http://ghostandthecity.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ghost &amp; The City&lt;/a&gt; who are a mix of jazz and indie.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  What inspires you?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
MATT: Lately I've been artistically inspired by the huge wave of creativity being displayed through the Instagram app. This isn't a plug for a client, it truly is a way to see how people all over the world are expressing themselves. The perspectives, color schemes, juxtapositions, and emotions seem to find their way into my thoughts when sketching out ideas for illustrations.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

At lease once a week I make a trip to the local book stores to hunt for sweet covers. That form of art when done well is smart, simple, and one step closer to pulling you into the story. It reminds me to not over-design projects.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Outside the art world, I'm inspired by the support I have from my family and witnessing the hard work and talents of my friends. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;You can check out Matt's poster, and the other Artcrank posters, at &lt;a href="http://www.chromebagsstore.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Chrome&lt;/a&gt; through the end of the week. Take a look at Matt's other work on &lt;a href="http://www.blackt-shirt.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;his site&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1675</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1675</guid>
      <title>50% off The Bubble Lounge</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1675/original.jpg?1321034542" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; We know you work hard, so you deserve to &lt;a href="http://lollercoaster.me/wp-content/uploads/2011/04/zzzzz.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;lounge hard&lt;/a&gt;. Perhaps you’re familiar with the cozy, romantic interior of The Bubble Lounge, but what you may not have heard about are the amazing food offerings. This tapas menu ensures you won’t have to lift a fork, spoon or knife to get this sustenance into your mouth. I’m talking buttery, flaky filo crusted hearts of palm, finger friendly sandwiches layered with Manchego cheese, prosciutto and green apple, cheese selections, and fresh strawberries with a pot of warm chocolate for dipping. And of course, the proper way to lounge is with drink in hand, which isn’t hard with a full bar, over 25 sparking wines and champagnes by the glass, over 250 by the bottle and tasting palettes featuring some of The Bubble Lounge’s most popular and unique champagnes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

The atmosphere at The Bubble Lounge is as versatile as their champagne menu. Reserve a corner couch in the back to celebrate your next birthday with 30 of your closest friends while staff keeps you supplied with the party juice, or tuck in to a table near the glass patio doors for an intimate date. Friday nights bring The Bubble Lounge’s Tiny Bubbles Party featuring alternative entertainment like burlesque shows, performance artists and DJs that know how to take your hand and lead you straight in to the weekend.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Cheers to that! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Filo Crusted Hearts of Palm w/ Prosciutto &amp; Parmesan, $12&lt;br&gt;
Manchego with Prosciutto and Green Apple Sandwich, $13&lt;br&gt;
Chicken Curry with Green Apple and Toasted Walnuts Salad, $11&lt;br&gt;
Fresh Strawberries with Warm Chocolate Fondue, $12&lt;br&gt;
Perrier Jouet Grand Brut Champagne/Glass, $16&lt;br&gt;
The Bubble Bellini – Prosecco and Peach Nectar, $14&lt;Br&gt;
Cashmere &amp; Silk Cocktail – Grey Goose La Poir, St. Germaine, Piper Heidsieck Champagne, $13&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Reserve a comfy couch space by calling 415-434-4204&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Tuesday – Thursday, 5:30 p.m. to midnight&lt;br&gt;
Friday, 5 p.m. to 2 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday, 6:30 p.m. to 2 a.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-16 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2011 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>The Bubble Lounge</location>
      <address>714 Montgomery St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94111</zip>
      <latitude>37.7959</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.403</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 434-4204</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1675/original.jpg?1321034542</image>
      <website>http://www.bubblelounge.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1681</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1681</guid>
      <title>50% off Nico's Tacos</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1681/original.jpg?1321049878" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Nico’s Tacos isn’t your typical taqueria, and because of that, we’d like to take you through a &lt;a href="http://youtu.be/0uuCNAwXGaQ?t=2m20s" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;little vocab lesson&lt;/a&gt; of some of the phrases you’ll see on the menu here. Lesson #1: &lt;i&gt;California Crakslaw&lt;/i&gt; – crisp cabbage, carrots and cilantro with a zesty garlic-lime vinaigrette. Lesson #2: &lt;i&gt;Guerilla Sauce&lt;/i&gt; – creamy chipotle aioli spiked with achiote (a spice) and Sriracha. Lesson #3: &lt;i&gt;Green Sauce&lt;/i&gt; – a creamy blend of avocado, sour cream, cilantro and a hint of lime. The theme here is a California twist on taqueria classics and a So Cal vibe throughout the restaurant. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Mainstays like tacos, quesadillas, burritos, nachos and platters make up most of the menu, but new additions like carne asada fries made with garlic curly fries and green sauce, teriyacos (teriyaki tacos) and weekend brunch chilaquiles (think breakfast nachos) spice up the menu as much as Nico’s homemade orange hot sauce – it’s a high level burst of temperature made with carrots and habanero peppers. Calm the fire with an adult beverage from an array of Mexican imports, or a more local beer like 21st Amendment’s canned IPA. And if you’re feeling really brave, test out the death oil hot sauce, it’s a concentrated concoction of oil from cooked habanero peppers. And if you make it through without steam coming out of your ears, you can rightfully tell people you cheated death. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Baja or Grilled Shrimp Quesadilla, $9&lt;br&gt;
Veggie Soyrizo Brown Rice Bowl, $7.50&lt;br&gt; 
Nachos, $7.75&lt;br&gt;
Chicken Tacos, $3.50&lt;br&gt;
Giant Pork Burrito, $8.50&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Thursday, 11:30 a.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Friday – Saturday, 11:30 a.m. to midnight&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, 11:30 a.m. to 9 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-15 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2011 23:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Nico's Tacos</location>
      <address>1310 Grant Ave</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94133</zip>
      <latitude>37.799</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.407</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 362-6163</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1681/original.jpg?1321049878</image>
      <website>http://www.nicostacossf.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2641</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2641</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do on the Weeknights, November 14-17</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2641/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1321221572" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Wouldn’t it be nice if humans were the type of animal that went in to hibernation to survive the winter? We could just feast our little brains out and then curl up under a mound of blankets only to emerge once the elements are a little less harsh. But, as much fun as that sounds, we don't want to miss out on this:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

THANKSGIVING DINNER PARTY AT THE HUB&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Tuesday, November 15, 6:30 to 8 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Here’s a good way to avoid the “I’m so full, I’m scared I’m going to pop” feeling you always get at the Thanksgiving dinner table: start training now. The Hub workspace is hosting a Thanksgiving Dinner at their SF office (Organic Roasted California Turkey, Heirloom Mashed Potatoes with Garlic Gravy, Sweet Potato Pie with Marshmallows, nom nom nom), and you're invited. Be sure to wear a long shirt in case you need to loosen your belt halfway through. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://thanksgivingathub.eventbrite.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets are $35&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1326" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Cumaica Coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

DIY HOLIDAYS AT 18 REASONS: PERSIMMONS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Tuesday, November 15, 7p.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you’re thinking &lt;i&gt;What the heck is a persimmon?&lt;/i&gt; right now, check out this little &lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/foodblogga/3050470243/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;photo reference&lt;/a&gt; for clarification. During this class, you’re going to learn more about the persimmon than you thought existed, including folklore and history, drying them, making candy from them and how to create charming gift baskets to share your new favorite fruit with your friends and family. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/208771" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets are $35&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1370" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Luna Park&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

ICE RINK IN UNION SQUARE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Through January 16, &lt;a href="https://www.imgtickets.com/OnlineCustom/default.asp?brand=SFIce" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Times and Tickets Here&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The annual holiday ice rink, sponsored by Safeway this year, has unfurled its icy surface. The rink is open until mid January, but you may want to start practicing your triple salchow on dry land now, before taking to ice. Skate rental is $5, but it’s BYOH (Bring Your Own Helmet). &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://unionsquareicerink.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Union Square Ice Rink&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1637" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;SB40&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2643</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2643</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>(Bacon) Crack Comes To Fatted Calf</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2643/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1321221312" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Yep, that’s right, we’re encouraging you to indulge in a little crack. Bacon crack, that is, from the Willy Wonka mind of Kai Kronfield, the man behind popular dessert pop-up, &lt;a href="http://noshthis.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Nosh This&lt;/a&gt;. So what’s in bacon crack? You better locate a tissue, because what you’re about to read is going to make you drool. Start with fried-to-a-crisp bacon mixed with butter-toffee, almonds and salt dipped in 72% chocolate. Hey, we warned you.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Kai’s treats are &lt;a href="http://noshthis.com/retail-partners/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;available in 10 stores around the Bay&lt;/a&gt;, including seven in San Francisco, and now he’s teaming up with Hayes Valley’s beloved charcuterie provider, &lt;a href="http://fattedcalf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Fatted Calf&lt;/a&gt;, to add their bacon-y deliciousness to his already mouthwatering treats. We’re talking bacon dry-rubbed with brown sugar, sea salt and spices and smoked over applewood. Kai says when he met a Fatted Calf staff member at one of his events, he told him he &lt;i&gt;needed&lt;/i&gt; to be in the store, and from there, the fit was just natural. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Nosh This debuted the Fatted Calf Bacon Crack last Wednesday during Fatted Calf’s pork happy hour with samples of the famous goodies. They’re now available for sale at the Hayes Valley and Napa locations. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Follow &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/NoshThis" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;@NoshThis&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/fattedcalf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;@fattedcalf&lt;/a&gt; to make sure you don’t miss a bite of what these innovative foodies are up to. </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1665</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1665</guid>
      <title>50% off Coffee Adventures</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1665/original.jpg?1320862013" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Usually, anything even close to the vicinity of Fisherman’s Wharf is a &lt;a href="http://www.coopersafety.com/Danger-Do-Not-Enter-This-Area.jpeg?id=472&amp;W=600&amp;H=600" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;no go zone&lt;/a&gt; for locals due to the heavy tourist population running rampant through the area. That’s understandable, but we shouldn’t deprive ourselves of one of the most beautiful parts of SF, and we really, really shouldn’t keep ourselves away from what is, in my travels and extensive taste tests, the best chai latte I’ve ever had. Owners Bob and Nicole know a lot about coffee (they say their coffee snobbery keeps them on top of the best ways to get the most out of a bean, like using cold pressed espresso for iced drinks, not watered down coffee), but you’d swear they invented the chai latte after you taste this thing. Using loose leaf tea, cinnamon, cardamom, cloves and Coffee Adventures’ own sweetening base (which I swear is made with magic and rainbows) they whip up a chai that’s creamy, silky and wholly addicting.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

The food menu boasts fresh pastries, paninis and salads, but it’s the daily specials that are the real sellouts, in the good way of selling out, I mean. Monday brings a spicy-ish jambalaya with sausage, rice and vegetables, Thursday is vegan chili and on Fridays you can dip in to Kickin’ Crab Sweet Corn Chowder. Which should all, of course, be accompanied by a side of chai latte. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Chai Latte (small), $2.70&lt;br&gt;
Avalanche Smoothie – ice cream or yogurt w/ espresso, white chocolate syrup, caramel syrup, $3.75&lt;br&gt;
Bistro Bagel Scram – bagel w/ egg, artichoke hearts, tomato, spinach, $4.50&lt;br&gt;
Chicken Panini w/ southwest chipotle pesto, provolone cheese, $6.50&lt;br&gt;
Portabella Mushroom Panini wi/ basil pesto, fire roasted red pepper, spinach, provolone cheese, $6.50&lt;br&gt;
Monday Special: Jambalaya – sausage, rice, vegetables, mildly spicy, $5.50&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Friday, 7 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday – Sunday, 8 a.m. to 7 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-14 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2011 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Coffee Adventures</location>
      <address>1331 Columbus Avenue</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94133</zip>
      <latitude>37.8062</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.419</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 441-0301</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1665/original.jpg?1320862013</image>
      <website>http://www.bestchaisf.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2616</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2616</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Caption This! Friday Photo Fun</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2616/BigThumb2.jpg?1320940047" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Give us your best witty caption to go with this extra curious pic on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

We'll post some our favorites to this here website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

As for this interesting image from last week, here are some of the caption contributions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src=" http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/seen/2579/captionthis.jpg?1320335671"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR FAVORITE:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Some people just want to watch the world burn."&lt;br&gt;
- Jaymin Nam

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;HONORABLE MENTIONS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Do you think they can see us?!"&lt;br&gt;
- Anne M. Standley&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Although the fashion never caught on like they thought it would, Nick and Lydia did not regret the decision to have their eyelids surgically removed."&lt;br&gt;
- Josh Phillipson&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Thyroid Awareness Month"&lt;br&gt;
- Emily Philp&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"It didn't take Dr. Finger long to recognize that his one-stop shop for proctology and photography didn't produce such great results."&lt;br&gt;
- Michael Rock&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"My God--it's full of stars."&lt;br&gt;
- John Donovan&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The icy water was already climbing up above their knees, and the ship was sinking fast... But their cruise tickets included a free portrait, and Bill and Joan were determined to get what they paid for."&lt;br&gt;
- David K. Wind&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Keep very, very still.... maybe he won't see us."&lt;br&gt;
- Evelyn Sam&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I like to make my nude models feel as comfortable as possible. I'll take my clothes off first...then you can remove yours."&lt;br&gt;
- Mike Byrne&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The photographer used a different kind of 'flash'."&lt;br&gt;
- Sean Hammac
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2616/BW2.jpg?1316724954</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2624</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2624</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do This Weekend, November 11-13</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2624/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320946837" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Eleven, eleven, eleven! Or, 11-11-11. Looks a little more like binary code than a date. Oh nerd jokes! Regardless, we still won’t be able to remember what day it is, but we would never, ever forget to mark our calendars for this:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

DOUBLE FEATURE AT CASTRO THEATRE + SCOUTMOB TREAT&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, November 13, Shows start at 2 p.m. &amp; 7 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This Sunday will feature more Queen than the Castro Theatre’s ever seen. At least thanks to Queen's rock score, heard throughout &lt;i&gt;Flash Gordon&lt;/i&gt;. Stay for &lt;i&gt;Dune&lt;/i&gt; and you’ll be rewarded with four foot tall shots of Sting’s abs. &lt;i&gt;Bring your not-yet-converted-to-Scoutmob-friends to the 4:10 or 7 p.m. shows for a buttery, salty treat.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.castrotheatre.com/p-list.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Castro Theatre&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1630" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Ike’s Place&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

FALL LUXURY CHOCOLATE SALON AT FORT MASON&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, November 13, 10 a.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The holiday season is synonymous with chocolate. Or maybe it’s just our lives that are synonymous with chocolate... either way, the Fall Luxury Chocolate Salon is the time to indulge with over 30 chocolatiers, confectioners and wineries. Get all your holiday gifting done here while fueling yourself through the shopping frenzy with bursts of chocolate.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://fallchocolatesalon2011.eventbrite.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Advance tickets are $20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1530" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;La Canasta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

MOVIES ON THE BUS WITH CHICKEN JOHN&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday November 11, 8 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Bet you never thought you’d be voluntarily boarding a bus with SF local &lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chicken_John" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Chicken John&lt;/a&gt;, but he’s inviting everyone aboard for a night of the movie &lt;i&gt;Network&lt;/i&gt; with intermission at a secret tea garden in Oakland then over to Grizzly Peak during the last half of the movie. The bus takes off from &lt;a href="http://ritualroasters.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ritual Roasters&lt;/a&gt; at 8 p.m. sharp!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/208799" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Admission is $20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1604" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;South End Grill ‘n’ Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1647</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1647</guid>
      <title>50% off Marmalade Boutique</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1647/original.jpg?1320715053" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; When’s the last time you went shopping with $100 and actually came home with change? And I’m not talking about a trip to the dollar store. Here at Marmalade, that’s exactly what you’re going to get: an exciting change in your wardrobe, along with some &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aPX5mRSQ3pw" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;change in your pocket&lt;/a&gt;, because nearly everything in the store is priced well under $100. And out here on Union Street, that’s basically unheard of. With brands like &lt;a href="http://www.michaelstars.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Stars&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://collectiveconcepts.net/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Collective Concepts&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.kersh.ca/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Kersh&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.sanctuaryclothing.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Sanctuary&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.ellamoss.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Ella Moss&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.splendid.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Splendid&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://veronicamclothing.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Veronica M&lt;/a&gt; offering up pieces that can go from desk to dinner, work to weekend, so you’re getting even more bang for your buck. &lt;i&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.luckymag.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Lucky Magazine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt; even described Marmalade as “Anthropologie style with an H&amp;M pricetag." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

But you won’t have to hunt through racks and racks to find your new favorite dress; Marmalade is a cozy (say hi to Clementine the goldfish in between trying on your new finds) store with carefully selected pieces that staff (all are trained stylists) can help you piece together in to an outfit to match your personal style. And, everything is ordered in small shipments with new merchandise hitting the shelves up to three times per week. That’s insurance you won’t run in to a million other girls wearing the same top. But as long as it’s from Marmalade, is that really such a bad thing?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Boutique Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Splendid Tops, $52&lt;br&gt;
Collective Concept Dresses, $68&lt;br&gt;
Volcano candles, $28&lt;br&gt;
Peppermint Tea Scarves, $24&lt;br&gt;
Marleybone &amp; High Street UK Cardigans, $58&lt;br&gt;
Sanctuary Denim, $68&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Saturday, 11 a.m. to 7 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, 11 a.m. to 6 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-11 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2012 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Marmalade Boutique</location>
      <address>2059 Union St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94123</zip>
      <latitude>37.7973</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.433</longitude>
      <phone>415-673-9544</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1647/original.jpg?1320715053</image>
      <website>http://www.marmaladesf.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2636</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2636</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Not Your Grandmother’s Scavenger Hunt</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2636/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320860359" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;When a scavenger hunt starts with slurping down beers from something called “Bongzilla” and dodging water balloons being thrown at you from rooftops, you know it takes a certain breed to emerge victorious. Such is the case at the &lt;a href="http://www.clashsf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;California League of Adult Scavenger Hunters&lt;/a&gt; events. Their next venture will take participants through the wild streets of the Castro in &lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="&lt;a href="http://www.clashsf.com/tight--bright.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tight &amp; Bright&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;, neon spandex required:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: How did this whole thing come about?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: How did it blossom?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Yessssss, how did it “blossom?”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: We started by trying to make a league out of scavenger hunts, much like soccer or some other sport, and it didn’t really work that well, but the result is what we have now, which is CLASH in it's current for, with hunts every Saturday night, sometimes Fridays. But, we’re going to take another shot at the league early next year. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: So how does a typical hunt begin?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: Way back when, we started them off in parks, but one time we brought out a bottle of Jameson and gave people shots before the teams took off, and since then, we’ve moved the start to bars. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Social lubrication. Brilliant. So then what?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: About half of the people shows up with their team of 5-6 players and the other half shows up as individuals or pairs, and we put them in to teams. Once everyone's arrived, we do some ice breakers. Sometimes we do an alley obstacle course involving beer, although the cops have been called a few times, and then we launch the teams off. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/scav_relay.jpg" alt="Scavenger Hunt Relay Race" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: And then during the hunt?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: The hunts usually last one and a half to two hours, and we have people dressed up as characters along the way, so there’s people to find, planted objects, strangers they have to interact with, even bonus points for spraying another team with silly string. The teams are taking photos the whole time, and a bit of drinking along the way, and when they get back to the bar, we download their photos and tally up their scores. Sometimes we have a bonus round, like a dance off, and we project the best photos from the night inside the bar and then declare the winners. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/scav_characters.jpg" alt="Scavenger Hunt Characters" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: So basically, your job is to make up games. That’s like the coolest thing ever. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: Yes, it is. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: What would your ultimate, dream scavenger hunt look like?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: With CLASH, we usually stick to one neighborhood, so it would involve a few different neighborhoods and a few different modes of transportation. Like those little yellow cars that you see all around the city, we’ve talked about getting a limo involved, so that would be part of it, public transportation... a lot of characters... and a lot of people on rooftops throwing water balloons at all the players. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Wow. Like a real life video game!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: Exactly! And also, there would be live animals. Tigers and zonkeys, maybe. Just something really extreme.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Like hard hats required?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: Hard hats, climbing up buildings, just pushing the limits. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/scav_bodyshot.jpg" alt="Scavenger Hunt SF" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: So tell us more about CLASH moving in to the league scene here in a few months. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
CLASH: We’re going to have a Tuesday night league that goes for four weeks, it’s called the CLASH Cup. And then our big hunts will just be one Saturday every month. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/tightbright.jpg" alt="Tight &amp; Bright" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Sign up for CLASH’s &lt;a href="&lt;a href="http://www.clashsf.com/tight--bright.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;next hunt here&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ClashScavengerHunts" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;like ‘em on Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and follow them on Twitter &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/clashsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;@clashsf&lt;/a&gt; for more league news.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2618</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2618</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>How To Overcome Name Attention Deficiency Disorder </title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2618/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320860396" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;There once was a man from Nantucket&lt;/i&gt;, whose name we can never remember and end up having to awkwardly introduce him to friends hoping he’ll take the initiative and say his own name first. Thankfully, for those of us who are faint of mind when it comes to remembering names, there’s a new app about to hit the block called &lt;a href="http://namerick.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Namerick&lt;/a&gt;, which promises, through science, to help you out with your &lt;a href="http://namerick.com/blog/got-nadds-name-attention-deficiency-disorder/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Name Attention Deficiency Disorder&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Ok, so what’s a namerick? According to the creators, it’s “a mnemonic device that utilizes imagery and alliteration to make a name more memorable.” Basically, once you meet someone, you wait for the chance to input their name in to Namerick (it auto-fills using US Census data for faster input), make notes on the person’s profession/relationship to you, then press the &lt;i&gt;Generate Namerick&lt;/i&gt; button which generates a memorable imagery and alliteration based off the person’s name. The app will also send you follow up texts reminding you of the person’s name so you can really get it ingrained into those little brain synapses. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Check out the video for a tutorial and inside look at what else the app can do. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width="510" height="307" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/nJdvpvkkWR4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Namerick just launched, so &lt;a href="http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/namerick-remember-names/id473146248" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;download the app for free now&lt;/a&gt;. We wouldn't want you to forget later. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

We’re digging you, Namerick, now what can you do about helping us remember where we put our sunglasses?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2011 02:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1641</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1641</guid>
      <title>50% off Indie Industries (North Beach)</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1641/original.jpg?1320789654" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; At Indie Industries, you don’t have to look for local tags to make sure you’re supporting your fellow city dwellers, all you have to do is look for an Indie Industries label on the garment or accessory you’ve got your eye on. The brand was founded in NYC by fashion design grads who brought their work together to form one strong company. Word quickly spread, and after getting picked up by over 50 retail shops, the design studio made its way west, eventually landing in San Francisco. You’ll find simple, solid color t-shirts, rainy weather scarves, neon limited edition jelly belts, and more, all stamped with the Indie Industries name. All good designers have a mass of inspirations, which is what the rest of the store is packed with. You’ll find top selling dresses from made-in-California companies like Do &amp; Be and MBD, and skirts that can keep up with the San Francisco weather by looking great paired with bare legs or tights. And for the gents, vegan hooded jackets that make you look as badass as &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=E0kkPK_WSck" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Lorenzo Lamas in &lt;i&gt;Renegade&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

But the art isn’t only wearable here at Indie Industries. There are shelves of items for a little fun in the kitchen as well. Cutting a cake is fine, but with a plastic kitchen Table Saw by Fred, you can &lt;i&gt;carve&lt;/i&gt; that bad boy. Even the salt shakers look a little more museum-worthy than kitchen cabinet find. And of course, anything emblazoned with a mustache is sure to catch our eye, which in this case comes in the form of a wine opener. Yep, we’re pretty sure we can’t live without it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Do &amp; Be Geometric Dress, $42&lt;br&gt;
Eklah Metallic Tribe Top, $32&lt;br&gt;
Qupid Black Heel Boots, $42&lt;br&gt;
Nuco Men’s Plaid Shirt, $39&lt;br&gt;
Custom Rags Vegan Hooded Leather Jacket, $89&lt;br&gt;
Sunglasses, $16&lt;br&gt;
Plastic Kitchen Table Saw, $8&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Saturday, noon to 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, noon to 8 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-10 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Wed, 09 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Indie Industries (North Beach)</location>
      <address>218 Columbus Ave</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94133</zip>
      <latitude>37.7974</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.406</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 986-7043</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1641/original.jpg?1320789654</image>
      <website>http://www.indieindustries.com</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2634</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2634</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Dog Tricks for City Humans</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sf_bigthumb1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2634/SF_bigthumb1.jpg?1320773633" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;San Francisco is a city of dogs. But dating complaints aside, this place is teeming with canines wagging for a walk. Everyone’s got special spots and secret tricks to owning a dog in the city, so here’s a quick insider’s guide to where to go, how to get there, and what to do if you’re craving a pup of your own. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Story and Illustrations By Rose Garrett&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Transportation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Good old-fashioned walking your dog is the best way to get to where you’re going with some exercise thrown in. But if you’ve got miles to go, SF public transpo might consider throwing you a bone&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;MUNI:&lt;/i&gt; If you don’t have a service dog, prepare to muzzle and leash your hound and travel only outside of the peak commuter hours of 5-9am and 3-7pm, which is kind of a bummer. And according to official MUNI rules, a fare equal to the owner’s must be paid for each non-service animal. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/dogs/charles.png" alt="Rose Garrett Dog Illustration" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;BART:&lt;/i&gt; Allows pets to be brought aboard at no additional charge, but stipulates that your animal “must be secured in a container that is specifically manufactured for transport of a pet,” which may work for your Chihuahua, but not so much for your Great Dane. Pets at-large or on a leash or harness (other than service dogs) are not permitted. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Caltrain:&lt;/i&gt; Has the stingiest policy of them all, allowing only service dogs onto their trains, with no exceptions. The workaround? Get your dog certified as an Emotional Support Animal (hey, we’ve all got issues), and you can take him on board with you every day. One Caltrain perk? Puppies in training for Guide Dogs for the Blind may board Caltrain at any time, so keep your eyes open for potential cute overload. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Dog-Friendly Spaces&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Dogs need room to roam, and SF has a bunch of options of choose from, whether you’re going for city parks or more rugged terrain.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Parks&lt;/i&gt;: Duboce Park is a classic, but such out-of-the-way spots as Bernal Park and Glen Canyon make for more secluded dog-walking. Visit the almost-secret Corona Heights Park for a dog run with a breathtaking view of the city (multitask by bringing a date on your evening walk and a visit to smooch castle is almost guaranteed). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/dogs/dalmatian_rotate.png" alt="Rose Garrett Dog Illustration" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Beaches &amp; Fields:&lt;/i&gt; Look to Fort Funston for a vigorous off-leash outing. Other options for letting your dog wild and free are Baker Beach (north of Lobos Creek), Land’s End, Crissy Field and Ocean Beach. Dogs should always be under “voice control,” so if your dog has discipline issues, consider taking him to training before letting him off the leash. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;(Doggie) Style&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Folks in SF probably pay more attention to their dog’s duds than their own (and it shows. Zing!). These SF purveyors provide local products for poochie:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.timbuk2.com/tb2/products/mutt-mover-dog-backpack" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Timbuk2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;:  The messenger bag maker’s Muttmover pack is perfect for biking with your smallish dog. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.gwengear.com/info.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;GwenGear&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;: Choose from SF-made collars, harnesses and leashes in a myriad of colors and patterns. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/dogs/hounddog.png" alt="Rose Garrett Dog Illustration" border="0" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://georgesf.com/index.asp" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;George&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;: Another SF company that covers the gamut from doggie tags to beds and sweaters—since 1991!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Get Your Own&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Do you frequent dog parks to stare creepily at other people’s pets? Maybe it’s time to get a pup of your own. These spots are the first places to look for canine companions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.rocketdogrescue.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Rocket Dog Rescue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;: This volunteer-run rescue organization saves dogs from being put down at over-crowded shelters and finds them loving, happy homes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.wonderdogrescue.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Wonder Dog Rescue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;: Wonder Dog rescues neglected puppies, elderly dogs, and everything in between, providing foster-care, medical care and adoption services.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.sfspca.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;SF SPCA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;: This go-to for all your adoption needs has the system down pat. Visit the SPCA to adopt a pet, or just to “look” at the impossibly cute kitties and pups (and then accidentally on purpose adopt one anyway). &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Rose is pretty awesome, isn’t she? How to live in the city with a dog is just the tip of the iceberg when it comes to all the cool stuff she knows about in SF. Check her out on Twitter &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/rose_garrett" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;@rose_garrett&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2608</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2608</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Win A Prize If You Recognize</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2608/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320773359" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;How well do you know your city? Give us your best guess on this mystery location and we'll send a sweet, sweet prize to one lucky winner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Reply to the Scoutmob daily email with your answer, or hit us up through &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/scoutmob" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.scoutmob.com/images/scoutmob_images/other_images/recognizedline.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2575/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320165030"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


Last week’s answer: Emmy's Spaghetti Shack&lt;br&gt;
Last week's winner: Kat Gaines</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2608/SM_home_Contentimage2.jpg?1316545886</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2617</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2617</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Mark Your Territory: Checking In The Old School Way</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2617/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320699750" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Well before there was Foursquare to let people know the mayor was in the house, all we had to rely on were animalistic basics like marking areas with our &lt;i&gt;ahem&lt;/i&gt; biological matter (read: pee). Welp, one guy has engineered a check in system that helps you &lt;a href="http://www.markyourterritory.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Mark Your Territory&lt;/a&gt; using an inherent behavior and new technology (read: “check-in to foursquare by physically urinating at the actual location”).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

The "meditation" hopes to maintain the technology of Foursquare while drawing humans back in to the physical world and providing additional information to others such as:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

+Check-In Gradient – How "there" were you?&lt;br&gt;
+Unbiased Profiles – A description of yourself that you cannot cheat&lt;br&gt;
+Cross-Species Communication – Squirrels knows nothing of your Foursquare status but can tell where you peed&lt;br&gt;
+True Ephemera – Maintenance of a physical reputation is demanding (and rewarding)&lt;br&gt;
+Indirect Environmental Restructuring – Explicit marks fade, but one's impact on a physical environment is permanent.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

This video should explain the many unanswered questions you probably have right now:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width="510" height="307" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/rRdfeb7vDWg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

And for how easy it seems to be to to relieve oneself on the sidewalk in SF, you should have no problem adopting this new way of checking in. 
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1637</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1637</guid>
      <title>50% off SB40</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1637/original.jpg?1320275898" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; If you don’t know where SB40 is, it’s all in the name. It stands for South Beach Pier 40, which is exactly where you’ll find this seafood-focused neighborhood sports bar. From this spot, you can &lt;a href="http://coe.berkeley.edu/news-center/publications/engineering-news/archive/engineering-news-vol-79-no-1f/bear-trivia-test-your-oski-knowledge/image_mini" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;take in a Cal game&lt;/a&gt; on one of the flat screen TVs while enjoying picturesque views of the U.S. Coast Guard vessels bobbing just outside the window. The glass top tables are covered in old timey San Francisco maps, perhaps a nod to the location’s original business, Carmen’s, which fed longshoremen in the area from 1957 to 2010. The ocean theme continues into the menu with starters like fresh oysters and lobster focaccia and entrées like the signature Boston-style lobster roll. But if you’d rather just look at the ocean than eat from it, the SB40 burger is a top seller. It comes piled with arugula, caramelized onions, house pickles and piri piri pepper with ocean views at no additional cost. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

The beer list is still growing, but already boasts staples like the dark and smoky Full Boar Scotch Ale and SB40’s house ale, which is similar to Sierra Nevada with a little less hop. And on our coveted sunny SF days, post up at one of the outdoor tables and watch the traffic along the Embarcadero. If it gets too overwhelming, shift slightly in your seat to bask in the serenity of the ocean and the deliciousness of your fresh catch. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Fresh Oysters, $2.50&lt;br&gt;
Lobster Foccacia, $9&lt;br&gt;
Boston-style Lobster Roll, $22&lt;br&gt;
SB40 Burger, $11&lt;br&gt;
Full Boar Scotch Ale, $5&lt;br&gt;
SB40 House Ale, $5&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday, 5 p.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Tuesday – Thursday, 11:30 a.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Friday – Saturday, 11:30 a.m. to 11 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, 11:30 a.m. to 6 p.m.
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-09 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Tue, 08 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>SB40</location>
      <address>The Embarcadero Pier 40</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94107</zip>
      <latitude>37.7817</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.388</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 222-6169</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1637/original.jpg?1320275898</image>
      <website>http://www.sb40sf.com</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2612</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2612</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Milkshake It All Around</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2612/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320700628" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Why isn't it called a milkblend, or a milkmix instead of a milkshake? We've only made a few of those bad boys in our day, but we don't remember much shaking going in to it. Perhaps it's because we start shaking with excitement whenever we get to slurp one of 'em down. Last week we asked you: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WHOSE MILKSHAKE BRINGS YOU TO THE YARD?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR SCOUT SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; Go big or go home, right? When I let myself indulge in the creamy goodness of a milkshake, I like to go huge. For me, that means heading to &lt;a href="http://www.pearlsdeluxe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Pearl's Deluxe Burgers&lt;/a&gt; for a craving killing Nutella shake. Add banana, and you could almost consider it a part of a well-balanced breakfast.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

I also have to throw a shout out for the spiked milkshake at &lt;a href="http://www.superdupersf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Super Duper&lt;/a&gt;, because even the most professionally made White Russian can't compare. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;YOU SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Super Duper."&lt;br&gt;
- Sophia Chung&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.melsdrive-in.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Mel's&lt;/a&gt;"&lt;br&gt;
- Helena Celdran Green&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://greenchilekitchen.com/chilepies/" target="_blank"&gt;Chile Pies &amp; Ice Cream&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;br&gt;
- Aylwin Po Villanueva&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The pecan pie shake at &lt;a href="http://goincoastalseafood.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Goin' Coastal&lt;/a&gt; is tasty!"&lt;br&gt;
- &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/tyrusasaurus" target="_blank"&gt;@Tyrusasaurus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;strong&gt;NEXT WEEK’S WHAT SAY YOU: WHO BREWS UP THE TASTIEST LOCALLY CRAFTED BEER?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href="http://anchorbrewing.com/beers/" target="_blank"&gt;Anchor Steam&lt;/a&gt; may have been around since before The Big One hit, but they're not the only brewers in the game. Hit us up on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and let us know whose beer has you saying &lt;i&gt;Once it hits your lips, it's so good!&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2603</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2603</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Food For Thought</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2603/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320632606" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We all know you should start your morning with a big healthy breakfast in order to have a good day, and &lt;a href="http://www.missiongraduates.org/blog/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Mission Graduates&lt;/a&gt;, a non-profit organization, helps K-12 students in the Mission start their lives off right by arming them with the support they need to get in to college. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Next Wednesday, with the help of Mission businesses, they’ll hold one of their biggest fundraisers, &lt;a href="http://www.missiongraduates.org/foodforthought/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Food For Thought&lt;/a&gt;, when restaurants will donate up to 50% of profits for that day to Mission Graduates. Nearly 30 restaurants are participating this year, and seats are filling up fast! Choose a restaurant from the list and &lt;a href="http://www.missiongraduates.org/foodforthought/?page_id=6" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;make a reservation&lt;/a&gt; now. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

That’s some of the most delicious food for thought we’ve ever come across. 
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2602</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2602</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do on the Weekdays, November 7-10</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2602/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320632771" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We hope you took advantage of that extra hour of sleep you got this weekend. Whether that means you were up extra late Facebooking stalking, er, "researching" that blind date you have this week, or actually sleeping is totally up to you. And if you forgot to adjust your clock and showed up at work at an awkward time, make sure it’s all sorted out by the time these events roll around:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

FARMERS MARKET HAPPY HOUR&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Wednesday, November 9, 2011 from 5:30 p.m. to 7:30 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
We’ve been eating our way through the Ferry Plaza Farmers Market for years, and now we’re learning we can drink our way through, too. &lt;a href="http://www.cuesa.org/" target="_blank"&gt;CUESA&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="http://norcalusbg.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Northern California Chapter of the United States Bartenders Guild&lt;/a&gt; are picking the best fall produce straight from the farmers’ stalls and mixing up some chilly weather cocktails to warm your heart, soul and body. Bites will also be appropriately paired. It’s the last happy hour of the season, so grab your ticket now. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://fallfarmersmarkethappyhour.eventbrite.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets are $35&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1398" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Fuzio Universal Bistro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

FREE CONCERT WITH YEAH YEAH YEAHS DRUMMER&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt; Tuesday, November 8, 8 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Ok, so you might not think of the cello as an instrument that would have a place in modern music, but Brian Chase, drummer for the &lt;a href="http://www.yeahyeahyeahs.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Yeah Yeah Yeahs&lt;/a&gt;, says it isn’t so, and he’s teaming up with the four talented musicians from &lt;a href="http://www.northskycelloensemble.com/NorthSkyCelloEnsemble.com/Home.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;North Sky Cello Ensemble&lt;/a&gt; for a free show at Brick &amp; Mortar. Show up early if you have any hopes of getting in. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.brickandmortarmusic.com/event/70881/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Brick &amp; Mortar Music Hall&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1440" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;We Be Sushi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

BLEK LE RAT: 30TH ANNIVERSARY RETROSPECTIVE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Thursday, November 10, 6:30 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you like Banksy, you’re gonna love Blek Le Rat. He’s one of the original modern street stencil graffiti artists, and a new book showcasing his art is available in the &lt;a href="http://museumstore.sfmoma.org/bllera30yean.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Museum Store&lt;/a&gt; and on display at the MOMA for a public viewing. The event is free, but we can’t promise you won’t be able to resist picking up a copy of the book. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.sfmoma.org/exhib_events/events/2004" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;SFMOMA&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1266" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Bar Basic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1630</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1630</guid>
      <title>100% off Ike's Place (16th St)</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1630/original.jpg?1320699727" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s &lt;a href="http://media.photobucket.com/image/baby%20cake%20face/HausYf/IMG_6184.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;somebody's birthday today&lt;/a&gt;. But it’s ok if you forgot a card, because you’re the one who’s going to be opening a birthday gift. Consider it a thank you for all you’ve done over the past four years. In 2007 (on today’s exact date), Ike Shehadeh, Ike’s Place’s owner, opened a regular ole sandwich shop and didn’t sell a thing (hard to believe, right?). He re-opened in November and was lucky to sell nine sandwiches. He decided to get a little creative, and &lt;i&gt;voilá&lt;/i&gt; – the Elvis Kieth was born. As the menu continued to grow, so did the business, until the original location had to close and Ike was forced to look for a larger space. After a short stay at temporary location that greatly tested the business, he’s finally settled in to his new spot on 16th near Sanchez, and thanks to your insatiable appetite for his sandwiches, things couldn't be going better. Even after three closures and two moves, Ike’s fans have been loyal and 2011 will bring record sales. As if Ike hasn’t thanked you enough by supplying you with consistently delicious sandwiches, he’s now giving away the creation that sparked a sandwich revolution.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Besides a list of sandwiches that could supply you with a new choice every day of the week for months, Ike’s followers know it’s all about the famous dirty sauce. It’s a garlic aioli that’s not only brushed in to the fresh bread baked here (gluten free also available!), but generously drizzled over all the ingredients before the sandwich is topped off with another piece of bread and wrapped tightly in brown paper for your to-go convenience.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

We’ve been to a few birthdays in our time, but the goody bags we got on the way out the door don’t even come close to what you’ll find in your Ike’s brown bag. Happy birthday, Ike’s Place, and you are so welcome. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Dirty Chips, $1.50&lt;br&gt;
Bottle Drinks, $2.49&lt;br&gt;
Can Drinks, $1&lt;br&gt;
Menage A Trois – halal chicken, real honey, honey mustard, bbq, pepper jack, swiss, cheddar, $11.11&lt;br&gt;
Matt Cain – roast beef, turkey, salami, godfather sauce, provolone, $9.99&lt;br&gt;
Paul Reubens – pastrami, homemade poppy seed coleslaw, french dressing, swiss, $9.99&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Thursday &amp; Sunday, 10 a.m. to 7 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Friday – Saturday, 10 a.m. to 10 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-08 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2011 02:59:00 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>100%</percentageOff>
      <location>Ike's Place (16th St)</location>
      <address>3489 16th St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94114</zip>
      <latitude>37.7645</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.431</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 553-6888</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1630/original.jpg?1320699727</image>
      <website>http://www.ilikeikesplace.com</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2588</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2588</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do This Weekend, November 4–6</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2588/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320345666" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Spring forward, Fall back. Yes! This Sunday night, when we’re all tucked snugly in to our beds, an extra hour of snoozing will be deposited into our sleep bank. Daylight Saving Time, you are saving me from being so darn tired in the mornings. At least for a few days until my body catches up and it’s back to guzzling coffee. Until the clocks make their magic jump, we’ll be keeping ourselves awake with these:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

MAD HATTER BOOZE TASTING&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday, November 4, 5:30 p.m. to 9:30 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If anyone knows how to throw a booze-fueled party, it’s &lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://drinkmemag.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Drink Me Magazine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;. Come drink like a crazy person at their Mad Hatter’s Grand Tasting featuring over 20 spirits, wine and beer purveyors.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://drinkmegrandtasting.eventbrite.com/?tour=31" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Get yer tickets here&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1566" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;L'acajou Bakery &amp; Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

FREE HOT DOGS ON BATTLE DAY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, November 6, 1 p.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
How do hot dogs and battles go together? Quite nicely according to Frankenart Mart. From November 6 to January 29, they’re showing and accepting art created under the theme of &lt;i&gt;battle&lt;/i&gt;. A free hot dog party will kick off the exhibition on November 6th when artists are asked to drop off their work. Free food and fun art? Hot dog! &lt;i&gt;Thanks to &lt;a href="http://sf.funcheap.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Johnny Funcheap&lt;/a&gt; for the heads up!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://frankenartmart.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Frankenart Mart&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1225" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Little Vietnam Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

FIRST FRIDAY ART OPENING AT D-STRUCTURE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Friday, November 4th, Show at 8 p.m., Reception at 8:30 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you’ve never been to one of &lt;a href="http://www.d-structuresf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;D-Structure&lt;/a&gt;’s raging first Friday art openings, well Son, you haven’t started living yet. Join artist &lt;a href="http://beerymethod.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Nick Beery&lt;/a&gt; as he shares his new installation (are ready for this?) &lt;i&gt;The Deathside: A Dark Tribute to Star Wars, Pop Culture, Underground Evil and a Deathly Farewell to the Repetitious Mutations of Fan Art&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;a href="http://redhook.com/age-gate/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Red Hook&lt;/a&gt; will be supplying you with all the libations you need. See something you like on the wall? Pick up your own print &lt;a href="http://www.d-structuresf.com/store/#ecwid:category=1764626&amp;mode=category&amp;offset=0&amp;sort=normal" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=285259451499332" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;RSVP here&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1548" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Hobson’s Choice Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2579</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2579</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Caption This! Friday Photo Fun</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2579/BigThumb2.jpg?1320335671" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Give us your best witty caption to go with this extra curious pic on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

We'll post some our favorites to this here website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

As for this interesting image from last week, here are some of the caption contributions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src=" http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/seen/2530/captionthis.jpg?1319729149"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR FAVORITE:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

‎"I will never regret this."&lt;br&gt;
- Joshua Thomas

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;HONORABLE MENTIONS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Here, kitty kitty..."&lt;br&gt;
- Vince Harris&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I want to....Roll and uhhh Roll all night and party every day..."&lt;br&gt;
- Tim Haynes&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The Insane Clown Posse tryouts were a total bust..not gonna mope about it though, gonna skate it out."&lt;br&gt;
- Katie Brinkworth&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Acid Wash holds no secrets."&lt;br&gt;
- Dallas Howell&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Oh crap, that's me, Pinetree Skatearama circa 1971."&lt;br&gt;
- Larry Bing&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Not many people realize King Diamond had a career before Mercyful Fate."&lt;br&gt;
- Bill Erwin&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"This is the move that almost got me into the Sarajevo olympics..."&lt;br&gt;
- Ella Greenstein&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Don't skate me because I'm beautiful."&lt;br&gt;
- Slade Gulledge&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Skate, and the world skates with you. Wear Kiss makeup, and you skate alone."&lt;br&gt;
- Rich Pasenow

</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2579/BW2.jpg?1316724954</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1636</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1636</guid>
      <title>50% off Bella Ceramica</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1636/original.jpg?1320270786" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s now November, people. Aside from prepping yourself for a ton of turkey and mountains of mashed potatoes you also have to start thinking about holiday shopping. It’s once again that &lt;a href="http://www.funny-potato.com/images/funny-family/family-pictures/christmas-family-picture.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;most wonderful time of the year&lt;/a&gt;–unless you decide to wait until Black Friday to get your loved ones something special, then it’s just miserable. Or even worse, what if you don’t know what to get them? Allow Scoutmob to make a suggestion: Bella Ceramica, offering the largest collection of fine Italian ceramics in Northern California.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Because the store is owned by Italian immigrant Claudio Luporini and his family, the extensive collection of ceramic goods that you see on display here are imported from the Italian region of Umbria–where Claudio knows many of the artists personally. Walking into their downtown location is very much like making your way into a gallery: artful pieces delicately line the walls, many of them of 4th generation craftsmanship; unique hand-painted patterns that have been handed down through hundreds of years.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Although the San Francisco store is just celebrating its one year anniversary, the Luporini family has been beautifying the homes of Bay Area-ites for over a decade from their original location in Oakland. Claudio brings style into your life with elegant dishware and dining sets, evoking pastoral scenes of the old-world countryside. It’s a lot more affordable than buying round-trip tickets to Italy. And, if you come in on Saturday, they’ll even validate your parking. Mamma mia!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Store Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Italian Proverb trays from Deruta, $18.95&lt;br&gt;
Simonetti hand-painted eggs from Castelli, starting at $40&lt;br&gt;
Simonetti hand-painted ornaments, $50-$125&lt;br&gt;
Niccacci Della Robbia pieces from Deruta, $50-$150&lt;br&gt;
Ceramic mugs from Deruta, Gubbio, Palermo and Siena, $40-$60&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Friday, 10 a.m. to 6 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday, 10 a.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Closed Sundays&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-07 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Fri, 04 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Bella Ceramica</location>
      <address>50 Post Street</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94108</zip>
      <latitude>37.789</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.403</longitude>
      <phone>415-837-1997</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1636/original.jpg?1320270786</image>
      <website>http://shop.bellaceramica.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2584</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2584</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>With Rice Paper Scissors, Everyone Wins</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2584/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320270760" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;They’ve been &lt;a href="http://travel.nytimes.com/2011/04/10/travel/10headsup-sf-market.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;featured in the &lt;i&gt;New York Times&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and even got a &lt;a href="http://www.missionmission.org/2011/08/11/anthony-bourdain-visits-rice-paper-scissors/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;visit from Anthony Bourdain&lt;/a&gt;, but &lt;a href="http://www.kitchensidecar.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Katie Kwan&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://ofcoursemag.wordpress.com/little-knock/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Valerie Luu&lt;/a&gt; say they started their popular Vietnamese food pop-up, &lt;a href="http://www.ricepaperscissors.com" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Rice Paper Scissors&lt;/a&gt;, simply because they “wanted to cook and serve people food on the street because that’s the way we enjoy eating.” If you’re ever walking down the street and see a cluster of little red stools, take our word for it, you HAVE to stop:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: How did you two meet?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
VALERIE: We meet when we were both hustlin’ Vietnamese street food at the Underground Market -- I was the Vietnamese crepe peddler, Katie was roasting whole pigs for her famous Banh Mi Burgers.&lt;br&gt;
KATIE: Quite the love story.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: When/how did the idea for Rice Paper Scissors form?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
KATIE: Five days before Tet, the Vietnamese New Year, when Valerie had the idea to get together and sell Vietnamese food in celebration of the coming new year.  What better way to do so than to line the street with little red stools and sell the Vietnamese food we have eaten through our travels and past experiences? Five days later, we found the perfect cherry blossom filled terrace, bought stacks of little red stools and cooked up crab glass noodles, stuffed fried chicken wings, and sea snail pho for 100 hungry eaters.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Take us back to your first big, official pop up. How did you feel going in to it?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
VALERIE: We felt an incredible high trying to put together a concept, menu, gig poster and find a space in just a few days. Everything had to come together so fast, we had no time to second-guess ourselves. We’re also lucky to have talented friends who are down to help with our crazy stunts: our friend &lt;a href="http://cargocollective.com/jessicataich#1348838/Rice-Paper-Scissors-Poster" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Jessica Taich&lt;/a&gt; whipped up our first gig poster in an hour, my boyfriend &lt;a href="http://foragesf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Iso&lt;/a&gt; was there taking orders while Katie’s BF &lt;a href="http://www.lowbicycles.com/lowbicycles/LOW_BICYCLES.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Andrew&lt;/a&gt; was helping her cook, and the original &lt;a href="http://www.thepizzahacker.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;PizzaHacker&lt;/a&gt; (aka Jeff Krupman) was there to untangle our Christmas lights -- super crucial.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: You guys cook every Thursday at &lt;a href="http://www.mojobicyclecafe.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Mojo Café&lt;/a&gt;. Does it make it any easier to work in a kitchen you’re familiar with?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
KATIE: We really enjoy cooking at Mojo and making it our Cheers spot. Every Banh Mi Thursday, we get to spend time with our friends and customers in a cozy cafe. Plus, we can work on perfecting our dishes without the added need to set up and break down a kitchen.&lt;br&gt;
VALERIE: Yeah, the less schlepping, the better.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: What are some of the challenges of having your kitchen on the street?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
KATIE: Setting up and breaking down, working with the San Francisco micro climates, and packing coolers with dry ice, are some of the less glamorous parts of the job. However, &lt;a href="http://www.ricepaperscissors.com/post/11361916126/pilgrimage-down-the-block-a-street-food-short" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;hitchhiking&lt;/a&gt; (as a last ditch effort) to our gig, working with different space allotments, and approaching small businesses to see if they are interested in hosting an RPS are some of the happy challenges that keep us on our toes. Valerie and I learned about cooking by selling street food so I would say the sidewalk is as familiar a kitchen as any.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: Think you’ll ever have a brick &amp; mortar?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
VALERIE: Hopefully!  We’re more likely to open a brick and mortar than a food truck.  The thought of parallel parking a beast of a truck makes me anxious. For now, we’re happy to call Mojo Cafe our home.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: What did we miss?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
RPS: We are thankful to all of the people who have lent their time, skills, and spaces to Rice Paper Scissors. Without them, this wouldn’t be quite the endeavor that it is.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/ricepapersf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Follow @ricepaperscissors&lt;/a&gt; and 
&lt;a href="http://www.ricepaperscissors.com/tipsheet" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;sign up for their Tipsheet&lt;/a&gt; to find out where they're popping up next.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Illustration by Tom Smith&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2589</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2589</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>You Are Listening To...</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2589/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320249784" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Ambient music. You hear it in elevators, artsy car commercials, and maybe even in your head before you nod off to sleep. It’s sleepy time music designed to stabilize your heart rate and make you feel like you're being swaddled in a big, fluffy cloud. Throw in a live feed from a police scanner, though, and the mood changes a bit.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;a href="http://www.antinomian.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Eric Eberhardt&lt;/a&gt;, video game product manager and website producer (and sometimes artist, apparently), &lt;a href="http://youarelistening.to/sanfrancisco" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;has mashed the two together&lt;/a&gt; to create something that honestly sounds a little otherworldly. Suddenly, reports of road rage and the possible sighting of a handgun don’t sound so scary set to the sounds of swirly acoustics. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Right now it’s only the CHP feed, but after listening to Eric’s creation for awhile, there’s a whole heck of a lot more that goes down on the streets beside flat tires and speeding. We’re digging you, ambient music/police scanner mashup, because we never thought experiencing someone getting pulled over could be so relaxing. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://uptownalmanac.com/2011/10/youve-had-long-day-sf-why-dont-you-come-take-your-shoes-load-your-weed-bong-and-listen-polic" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Thanks to Uptown Almanac for alerting us to this coolness.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1625</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1625</guid>
      <title>50% off Indie Industries (Castro)</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1625/original.jpg?1320166157" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Feeling Fashionable?  Indie Industries covers your back--and most other parts of your body as well, offering men's and women's clothing, accessories and designer jewelry all designed locally here in the Bay.  In fact, much of what you see in their new Market &amp; Castro location was created right in the store itself.  With its own live design studio, customers can &lt;a href="http://www.lememe.com/wp-content/uploads/2011/10/4.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;watch&lt;/a&gt; a crew of talented local artists as they fabricate the jewelry and assorted artful apparel that gives this shop its prolific personality.  We’re talking a happy hodge-podge of fabrics, foot-ware, fixtures and furnishings.  Denim, graphic Ts and re-purposed necklaces are just some of the alluring items that highlight this eclectic ensemble.  You’ll also find a bevy of small treasures that await your discovery.  Don’t be surprised if you leave the store with a new set of light bulbs.  Or if it’s too bright you can get yourself some cheap sunglasses, for under $20.

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And the artists aren’t just employees, they’re also the bosses here at one of the city’s only designer-owned collectives.  Sure, you &lt;em&gt;could&lt;/em&gt; go to a traditional department store and separate yourself from all this pesky creativity, but...you live in San Francisco, for cripes sake!  Winter is on the way.  Stave off the cold with that warm and fuzzy feeling that comes from supporting your friendly neighborhood design collective.   

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indie industries is at the threshold of art and style, somewhere between fashion boutique and showroom.  So step inside and wrap yourself in inspiration--although one of their reasonably-priced scarves would also do the trick.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Store Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Leather wallets made in SF by FullyCo, $24&lt;br&gt;
Handmade earrings and necklaces by Jenn Kubat, starting at $16&lt;br&gt;
Belts made to order by Jawn McQuade, starting at $14&lt;br&gt;
Graphics Tees made in-house, starting at $18&lt;br&gt;
Hand blown glass terrariums by Mike Stone, from $16-$85&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Sunday, 12p.m. to 9p.m.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-04 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Thu, 03 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Indie Industries (Castro)</location>
      <address>2352 Market St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94114</zip>
      <latitude>37.7635</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.434</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 861-1150</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1625/original.jpg?1320166157</image>
      <website>http://www.indieindustries.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2581</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2581</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>San Francisco’s Forrest Gump </title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2581/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320164848" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The movie &lt;i&gt;Forrest Gump&lt;/i&gt;, was just that, a movie. While it would be fun to imagine one person could possibly have been involved in just about every poignant moment in history from the 50’s to the 80’s, it just seems a little... unbelievable. Lawrence Ferlinghetti’s life seems a bit similar to Forrest’s, only there’s no script or well rehearsed acting here. He founded &lt;a href="http://www.citylights.com/" target="_blank"&gt;City Lights Books&lt;/a&gt; (where he sold Allen Ginsberg’s &lt;i&gt;Howl&lt;/i&gt; and was arrested on obscenity charges for it) in 1953, studied at Columbia, the Sorbonne and the Academie Julien in Paris, and has shared his poems and paintings all over the world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

This Friday, at the majestic &lt;a href="http://meridiangallery.org" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Meridian Gallery&lt;/a&gt;, Lawrence will read his newest poem &lt;i&gt;At Sea&lt;/i&gt;. His friend and fellow poet, Jack Hirschman, will join, reading from his new &lt;i&gt;Arcana&lt;/i&gt; before the two settle in to talk about the amazing lives they’ve lead while we all listen, wide-eyed. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Tickets are $10-$20 and available at the door or through &lt;a href="https://www.brownpapertickets.com/event/199583" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Brown Paper Tickets&lt;/a&gt;. </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2575</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2575</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Win A Prize If You Recognize</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2575/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320165030" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;How well do you know your city? Give us your best guess on this mystery location and we'll send a sweet, sweet prize to one lucky winner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Reply to the Scoutmob daily email with your answer, or hit us up through &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/scoutmob" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.scoutmob.com/images/scoutmob_images/other_images/recognizedline.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2526/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1319567861"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


Last week’s answer: The Fry-fecta at Roam Artisan Burgers&lt;br&gt;
Last week's winner: Yvette Cuca</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2575/SM_home_Contentimage2.jpg?1316545886</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1624</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1624</guid>
      <title>50% off Mark's Bar</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1624/original.jpg?1320077230" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Polk Gulch has such a sweet &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OW7N3ziIlFw" target="_blank"&gt;ring&lt;/a&gt; to it. It hearkens back to a golden age,
when Polk’s long commercial strip between Market and Geary was a high-end glamour destination for
glitterati all over the city. Owner Mark Aloiau remembers that era well, and is ready to help usher Polk Street
into its renaissance period. With his brand-new venture, Mark’s Bar, he colonized the old Lush Lounge
space at Polk and Post, re-purposing it with a bright, Asian flair (think fresh, tropical flowers, intricate wood
carvings, and parasols). Aloiau has been getting to know his neighbors, shopping nearby for everything
from fresh fruit to the gorgeous salvaged wood bar. The space is classy, but the drinks are affordable.
Happy hour prices are $3 for domestic beers and $4 for well drinks, with all-day specials like $7 for a Tecate
and a shot of 1800 Silver tequila. And for the fancy crowd, Mark has hand-crafted a portfolio of artisan
cocktails, including the Ginger Manhattan, with light rye whiskey, Cointreau, ginger syrup, and muddled
cucumber; the Wasabi Martini (exactly what it sounds like); and the Island Style, with Cîroc coconut vodka,
guava, orange, and lime juice, and grenadine. Mark’s Bar also serves a Tahitian beer called Hinano that’s
remarkably addictive, not to mention hard-to-find.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Which is all to say that this right now is your chance to get in on the goodness while this bar is still in its infancy. Before its old school charm is 
discovered... and you end up having to jockey for position at the bar. Trust us: it’s a treat.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;hr&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Ginger Manhattan, $10&lt;br&gt;
Wasabi Martini, $10&lt;br&gt;
Island Style Cocktail, $10&lt;br&gt;
Tecate and a shot of 1800 Silver Tequila, $7&lt;br&gt;
Hamms and a shot of George Dickel whiskey, $7&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday - Friday, 3 p.m. to 2 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday - Sunday, 1 p.m. to 2 a.m.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-03 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Mark's Bar</location>
      <address>1092 Post St.</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94109</zip>
      <latitude>37.7869</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.42</longitude>
      <phone />
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1624/original.jpg?1320077230</image>
      <website />
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1604</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1604</guid>
      <title>50% off South End Grill 'n' Bar</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1604/original.jpg?1319669324" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Mac ‘n’ Cheese?  Yes, please!  It’s always a smart move venturing into the warm confines of a friendly neighborhood eatery, but you need not be a genius to step up to this Mac bar. Boasting 10 varieties of the comfort food classic, South End Grill ‘n’ Bar satisfies the senses with an assortment of dazzling dishes that fill your belly with deliciousness and your mind with the memories of meals that mom used to make–if she happened to be an &lt;a href="http://www.simpalife.com/wp-content/uploads/Paula-Deen.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;incredibly talented cook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

Owner Steve Silver is half Jewish, half Asian and wholly charismatic. His menu is equally as eclectic, offering Italian specialties, like irresistible Chicken Milanese, alongside chic Chinese fare, like seared Hangar Steak on a billowing bed of bok choy. The food is sensational across the board, but the prices are downright unbelievable: enjoy a hearty entrée along with a pint of one of their six rotating Northern California micro-brews for around $15 (or half that, if you’re dining with the ‘Mob)! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

In addition to fan favorites like the Carbonara Mac–infused with green peas, crispy bacon and zesty Parmesan cheese–South End also dishes out finger friendly bar bites like pulled pork sliders and spiced rubbed wings, but don’t be surprised if you find yourself coming back to the mac ‘n’ cheese bar. Be forewarned: the crackly crunch of fried breadcrumbs atop a smattering of tasty cheeses is highly habit-forming. Casual and considerately quaint, South End Grill ‘n’ Bar fits perfectly into our cozy City By the Bay. Simply good food by a lifelong neighborhood native: a recipe for many happy returns.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Mac ‘n’ Cheese w/ cheddar, jack, Parmesan, and breadcrumbs, $7.50&lt;br&gt;
Carbonara Mac, $10&lt;br&gt;
Chicken Milanese served w/ arugula, mozzarella, and tomato, $12.50&lt;br&gt;
Asian Hangar Steak served w/ bok choy, $12.50&lt;br&gt;
Angus Beef Burger served w/ fries, $8&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Thursday, 5 p.m. to 10:30 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Friday &amp; Saturday, 5 p.m. to 11:30 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Closed Sundays&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-02 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>South End Grill 'n' Bar</location>
      <address>1499 Valencia St.</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94110</zip>
      <latitude>37.7493</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.42</longitude>
      <phone>415-648-8623</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1604/original.jpg?1319669324</image>
      <website>http://www.southendsf.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2561</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2561</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Getting Dressy For The Holidays</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2561/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1320087819" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;November 1st. There may not be a Hallmark card for it, but it is the official beginning of the holiday season. For the next two months, you’ll be gift shopping, whipping up potluck dishes, and party hopping. And you’ve gotta look good throughout the whole storm. Last week we asked you: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WHERE DO YOU GET OUTFITTED FOR THE HOLIDAYS?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR SCOUT SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; I get overwhelmed by ginormous department stores that seem to have racks and racks of choices, so much so, that I end up leaving with nothing. So the first time I popped in to &lt;a href="http://www.revolversf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Revolver&lt;/a&gt; and realized I would love to wear anything from their carefully selected wardrobe, it shot to number one on the list of stores I hit on shopping adventures. Be sure to check out the backroom, which is half art gallery, half super awesome sales rack. Hm, maybe I can get an advance on my Christmas money. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;YOU SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://ambiancesf.com/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Ambiance&lt;/a&gt; on Haight!!"&lt;br&gt;
- Nikki Marucut&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Nothing says holidays and shopping more than a spin through Macy's."&lt;br&gt;
- Adam Arlington&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The boys at The Common make me look like I actually know something about fashion."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
- Will Boston&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I feel ready to take on the chaos of the holidays in anything from Acrimont."&lt;br&gt;
- Angela Mason&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Mingle on Union is my favorite spot no matter what time of year."&lt;br&gt;
- Vanessa Spano&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I can always find something elegant but original at Painted Bird."&lt;br&gt;
- Armisen Matthews&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I never leave Welcome Stranger empty-handed."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
- Jack Richardson&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;strong&gt;NEXT WEEK’S WHAT SAY YOU: WHOSE MILKSHAKE BRINGS YOU TO THE YARD?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

When you were little your mom always encouraged you to drink your milk. Welp, she’s not around, so we’re encouraging you to drink your milkshake. Who mixes up this most delicious indulgence? Hit us up on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2565</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2565</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Arianna Orland Makes Posters That Rock</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2565/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1320087622" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;It started with the need to get her hands dirty, and a little inspiration from a phrase she saw stenciled in the Mission. Arianna Orland makes “words to live by” on “posters that rock.” So what does that look like? Just like this:

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/todaywasgood.jpg" border="0" alt="Today Was a Good Day Poster" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

She’s constantly scribbling down notes with new phrases, but only a few make the cut:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  You gotta tell us, where did the inspiration for your posters come from?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: As a designer who spends most of her time on the computer, I was looking for a way to get back to the roots of my craft and my profession so I decided to take a letterpress class. The first class project is to print any phrase you'd like. I have to say it was kind of a daunting moment. It felt a bit like I'd been mute my whole life and could suddenly speak a complete thought for the first time. Many years ago in the Mission District of San Francisco an artist had gone around stenciling phrases on the sidewalk to a lover. One of the phrases was "Love Me Till My Heart Stops". I took a photo of that and had it on my desk for  years. When it was my turn to choose a phrase to print, those are the letters I pulled from the drawer. After I saw them on the page I realized how powerful a few well chosen words could be.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  They’re so simple, but catchy. How do you decide on what’s poster-worthy?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: I keep a running list that I add to whenever a phrase comes to mind. You never know when you'll get a good idea; they end up on paper, notes in my iPhone, on the back of my hand. Before printing a new edition, I go through the list with Steve (partner at &lt;a href="http://www.activatestudio.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Activate Design Studio&lt;/a&gt;) to make the final edit. We usually end up with several from the running list and one or two that sneak up at the end in one of those "awww yeah...that's the move right there...we have to do that one" kind of moments.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  Are there any phrases you try to live your life by/find especially meaningful?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: Depends on the day. I spent this weekend in Los Angeles with my family. Right about now I'm feeling Today Was a Good Day &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  You say that your posters are “hand pulled.” What does that mean exactly?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: All posters are printed by me, by hand, on a Vandercook letterpress using 10 line gothic wood type. I cut the paper, I set the type, I ink the press, I feed the sheets, and walk them down the press one at a time.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  Where do you do your printing?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: I printed the first edition at &lt;a href="http://studioonthesq.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Studio on the Square&lt;/a&gt; in New York City. The second edition was printed at the &lt;a href="http://sfcb.org/" target="_blank"&gt;San Francisco Center for the Book&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  You currently have 12 posters in the “San Francisco collection.” Any plans to add more?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: Yes, look out for the next collection on the new year. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT:  You started the posters as a way to get out from behind the computer and dirty your hands up a little bit. Any other crafty projects in the works?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
ARIANNA: I have a &lt;a href="http://tatt.ly/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;tatt.ly&lt;/a&gt;, design temporary tattoo, coming out soon. And I will be at the &lt;a href="http://www.renegadecraft.com/holiday-sf" target="_blank"&gt;Renegade Holiday Craft Fair&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Get your hands on Arianna’s posters at &lt;a href="http://www.paperjampress.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Paper Jam Press&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2560</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2560</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Dip In To These Fantastic Fry Spots</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2560/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1319832861" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Drinking (which we don't doubt you'll be doing a little of tonight) and fries go together like vodka and soda. Some people might say fries are the perfect side dish, but put a plate of these crispy, fried deliciousnesses in front of our face, and we can make a meal out of it. It all starts with the fry, but can reach other worlds paired with the right dips. We rounded up just a few of our favorite fry dishes, from the French version to the Peruvian and a few more in between. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;All images via &lt;a href="http://www.foodspotting.com" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Foodspotting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/fries/nopa.jpg" border="0" alt="NOPA's Kennebec French Fries" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;NOPA’s LINK Kennebec French Fries and Red Pepper Feta Dip ($6)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.foodspotting.com/reviews/862320" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Spotted by Pei Ketron&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/fries/absinthe.jpg" border="0" alt="Absineth's French Fries" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Absinthe’s LINK French Fries with smoky tomato ketchup and sweet-onion aïoli ($6)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodspotting.com/reviews/409992" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Spotted by Sylphi&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/fries/pearls.jpg" border="0" alt="Pearl's Deluxe Burgers Sweet Potato French Fries" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Pearl’s Deluxe Burgers LINK Sweet Potato Fries ($3.49)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodspotting.com/reviews/944790" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Spotted by Fox W&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/fries/jakes.jpg" border="0" alt="Jake's Steak French Fries" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Jake’s Steaks LINK Waffle Fries ($4.29)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodspotting.com/reviews/256860" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Spotted by Pixelboy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/fries/limon.jpg" border="0" alt="Limon Rotisserie's Yucca Fries" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Limon Rotisserie’s LINK Yucca Fries ($3), Aji Sauces: Rocoto, Aji Amarillo, Chimichurri (.75 ea)&lt;/strong)&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodspotting.com/reviews/348563" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Spotted by James Guigayoma&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2557</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2557</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do on the Weeknights, October 31 – November 3</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2557/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1319832941" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We’re partied out, and technically Halloween just started. Darn you holidays that fall on weekdays, you always throw us off. At least if we stay in tonight, we can get up early to wait for the stores to open so we can buy up all the discount Halloween candy. And we’re not holding back, because our planned events this week are all completely free:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

GHOST WALK AT CITY HALL&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Monday, October 31, 6:30 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Politics can be scary. SF City Guides says Civic Center used to be the site of a cemetery, and that’s just one of the spooky tidbits you’ll learn about during this free tour. It only happens once a year on All Hallow’s Eve, and even though you might be scared out of your wits, leave your mace at home, you will be subject to a security search.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.sfcityguides.org/desc.html?tour=31" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;SF City Guides&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1480" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Barrel Room Wine Bar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

ONE CITY ONE BOOK: MARY ROACH IN CONVO WITH ADAM SAVAGE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Wednesday, November 2, 6 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Even if you haven’t read Roach’s &lt;i&gt;Packing for Mars&lt;/i&gt;, you’ll still enjoy her talk with &lt;i&gt;MythBuster’s&lt;/i&gt; Adam Savage. This is the best-selling, Oakland author’s 4th book, and the talk will start with a premiere of &lt;i&gt;Rockets of Yesterday&lt;/i&gt;, a video tour of 50s and 60s rockets. Seating is limited, so we recommend getting there as early as possible. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.sfpl.org/index.php?pg=2000387701" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;One City One Book&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1326" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Cumaica Coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

ALTERED BARBIES AT SHOTWELL 50&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Through November 20, Mon–Sat: 1 p.m. to 8 p.m., Sun: 1 p.m. to 5 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
A little hair of the dog for you when it comes to spooky, ghoulish, gruesomeness. Barbie may be one of America’s most recognizable icons, but not after these artists get to her with some scissors, glue and other craft materials. It's the artistic form of plastic surgery. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.shotwell50.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Shotwell 50&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1502" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;HANGR 16 Boutique&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1596</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1596</guid>
      <title>50% off Pizzeria Avellino</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1596/original.jpg?1319497414" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Pizzeria Avellino is &lt;a href="http://www.availableimages.com/images/pictures/2003/old-school/aph_0.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;old school&lt;/a&gt;. So old school, they not only have the staple red and white checkered tablecloths on all the tables, but the Giants memorabilia on the walls is from back in the day when the team called New York their home. But, that all makes sense since this pizza joint specializes in thin crust, New York style pizza. With whole milk mozzarella cheese from the happiest cows in Wisconsin and your choice of 15 toppings, including meatballs (duh, it’s an Italian restaurant), atop daily made dough (a family recipe from the owner’s grandparents), you’re gonna be asking who this Avellino is and how he gets his pizza to taste this darn delicious. Avellino is actually a city just outside Naples, Italy, the birthplace of all things pizza-licious. Personalize an individual slice, or go for the whole shebang, like the regular’s favorite Lombard Combo, a heavy sprinkling of pepperoni, sausage, mushrooms and black olives. And for dessert, another pizza, the Nutty Pizzetta, topped with hazelnut, chocolate cream and chocolate chips.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

In the mornings, the smells of mozzarella and fresh dough give way to coffee beans when Pizzeria Avellino transforms in to Café Avellino and serves up fresh brewed caffeine to Cow Hollow residents and everyone headed into the Presidio for work. Grab a bagel (pizza’s more portable cousin) stuffed with bacon and cheese  to hold you over until the Pizzeria opens at 11. Look for a full brunch to make its way on to weekend menu soon, because we all know there’s nothing wrong with pizza for breakfast. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Lombard Combo – pepperoni, sausage, mushrooms, and black olives, Large $24.50&lt;br&gt;
Meat Lovers – pepperoni, meatball, bacon, Large $23.50&lt;br&gt;
Cheese Slice, $3 (add .50 per topping)&lt;br&gt;
Caesar Salad, $6.75&lt;br&gt;
Nutty Pizzetta, Small $6.75, Large $9.50&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Cafe: &lt;br&gt;
Monday - Friday, 7 a.m. to 11 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday &amp; Sunday 7:30 a.m. to 11 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
Pizzeria: &lt;br&gt;
Saturday &amp; Sunday, 11 a.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Monday &amp; Tuesday, 11 a.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Wednesday &amp; Thursday, 11 a.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Friday, 11 a.m. to 11 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-11-01 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Tue, 01 May 2012 23:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Pizzeria Avellino</location>
      <address>2769 Lombard St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94123</zip>
      <latitude>37.7984</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.447</longitude>
      <phone>415-776-2500</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1596/original.jpg?1319497414</image>
      <website>http://pizzeriaavellino.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2530</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2530</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Caption This! Friday Photo Fun</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2530/BigThumb2.jpg?1319729148" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Give us your best witty caption to go with this extra curious pic on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

We'll post some our favorites to this here website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

As for this interesting image from last week, here are some of the caption contributions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src=" http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/seen/2488/captionthis.jpg?1319125396"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR FAVORITE:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Dude, I swear she just looked right. at. us."&lt;br&gt;
- Jeffrey Bryant Edwards

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;HONORABLE MENTIONS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

‎"Smokin' in the boys room."&lt;br&gt;
- Slade Gulledge&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Why did we eat that acid and come to school?"&lt;br&gt;
- Zack Miller&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Give us your lunch-money, nerd!"&lt;br&gt;
- Jeff Leiboff&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Hey, did those breakers just call us potheads?"&lt;br&gt;
- Jon Sanchez-Casas&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"And so, equipped with a Sears boombox and radically-tinted lenses, Papa's Pornstache gave rap metal its inauspicious start."&lt;br&gt;
- Joseph Thurston&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"After their 4H meeting, Brad, Alan &amp; Twiggy headed over to the local Tasty Freeze to hunt for prom dates."&lt;br&gt;
- Sean Madden&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

‎"DUDE! You were supposed to bring the Lynyrd Skynyrd tapes, not the Def Leppard!"&lt;br&gt;
- Villate Brown McKitrick&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Quit taking pictures. You're late for denim club."&lt;br&gt;
- Joshua Thomas&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Back then, it was so much easier to look cool. One quick trip to Denim-mart and you were well on your way."&lt;br&gt;
- Alex Garber
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2530/BW2.jpg?1316724954</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1600</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1600</guid>
      <title>50% off Pacific Catch (Chestnut Street)</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1600/original.jpg?1319670802" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; I really dislike standing around waiting for things, especially when my stomach is rumbling. Thanks to the power of the internet and a little pre-planning, you can have your Pacific Catch order in your hands as soon as you step off Chestnut and through the door. &lt;a href="http://pacificcatch.munchaway.com/locations/display_locations?order_mode=other&amp;locations_in_state=California" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Place your order online&lt;/a&gt; as soon as you feel the first bit of hunger, and by the time you swing in to grab your food, your stomach will be doing &lt;a href="http://spiderdiaries.richmond.edu/andrew14/files/2011/05/gymnastics_-_olympic_games.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;happy cartwheels&lt;/a&gt;. How fast you can rip open the package and get it in your mouth is up to you.  &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Pacific Catch is well known for its seafood offerings, but if you’re in the mood for something a little more “landfaring,” the Marina location now serves juicy, marinated grilled steak that can be added to any dish. Tucked inside an island taco and topped with crispy sweet onions, cabbage and Sriracha aioli, you’re gonna wonder where this dish has been all your life. And for the seafood lover, you’ve come to the right place. Hawaiian poke, salmon, mahi mahi, shrimp, ahi... I don’t think I need to keep tantalizing your taste buds. Add it to a salad, a sandwich, a taco or a rice bowl and you might be pushing your chopsticks aside for the biggest spoon you can find. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;If ordering online, show your Scoutmob deal at pickup and your credit card will be refunded the proper discount amount.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Sweet Potato Fries w/ ginger wasabi aioli &amp; sweet thai chili sauces, $5&lt;br&gt;
Pacific Steak Taco Platter w/ fries or salad, $11&lt;br&gt;
Japanese Wasabi Bowl w/ Grilled Salmon, $13.50&lt;br&gt;
Chipotle Mahi Mahi Salad, $12&lt;br&gt;
Spicy Ahi Sandwich w/ fries or salad, $11&lt;br&gt;
Agave Sparkling Lemonade, $3.50&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Daily, 11 a.m. to 10 p.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-10-31 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Pacific Catch (Chestnut Street)</location>
      <address>2027 Chestnut Street</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94123</zip>
      <latitude>37.8007</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.437</longitude>
      <phone>415-440-1950</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1600/original.jpg?1319670802</image>
      <website>http://www.pacificcatch.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2551</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2551</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do This Weekend, October 28-30</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2551/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1319731412" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Hopefully you’ve already locked down your Halloween plans and have five transportation backups planned for how you’re going to get around town all weekend. Lord knows you’re not getting a cab, and probably not a bus either. We got so desperate one year, we flagged down a delivery truck who ever so graciously delivered us to our house party destination (and we weren’t even wearing a sexy costume!). You’ll be partying the night away, but we’ve got you covered for that time of day when the zombies and vampires are safely tucked away:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

MUSTACHE RIDE OVER GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday, October 29, 1 p.m. to 9:30 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Who wants a mustache ride?! You provide the bike and mustache, and The Mustache Riders will make it happen. This is a pre-‘Movember event, and since you’re going to need strength and stamina to give it all you’ve got next month, it’s a good thing you’re training now. Don’t forget to bring some cashola for the ferry back. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=243487449035310" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;More details&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1530" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;La Canasta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

LEARN HEROIC TAROT READING&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, October 30th, 2 p.m. to 4 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
What better way to scare the bajesus out of your friends than predicting their futures using tarot cards? This Sunday, at the city’s House of DIY, workshop, learn “Major and Minor Arcana, the Court cards, and the the elemental suits.” Then go home and practice your serious face for when the Death card gets flipped over.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.workshopsf.org/?page_id=140&amp;id=890&amp;date=2011-10-30" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Details&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1299" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Fillmore Street Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

COME OUT AND PLAY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday, October 29, 7 p.m.  – Sunday, November 6, 6 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
“Can Timmy come out and play?” This version of Come Out and Play is only for the big leaguers. With the entire city as your game board, you’ll participate in over 15 free, real-life games that make regular old Capture the Flag look like the easiest thing in the world. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://comeoutandplaysf.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Full game schedule &amp; details&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1402" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;La Victoria Mexican Bakery &amp; Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1563</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1563</guid>
      <title>50% off Tony's Cable Car Restaurant</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1563/original.jpg?1318878046" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Sock hops, drive-ins, soda jerks and going steady; to some of us, these are things we’ve only ever seen in &lt;i&gt;Grease&lt;/i&gt;, to others, it’s the good old days. Tony’s Cable Car Restaurant, operating from the same location (with virtually the same menu) since 1972, is a step back to a time before Shape-Ups, street food carts and &lt;a href="http://serverseven.com/food/wp-content/uploads/2010/09/Bluetooth-Headset.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;phone accessories that clip on your ear&lt;/a&gt;, if you can even imagine. Here, you can still get a quarter pound hamburger for under $5 and a shake so thick, you might want to start working your mouth out now to ensure you can conquer it. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

It’s well after lunch hour by the time I jump off the 38 and scoot up and down the hill to Tony’s Cable Car Restaurant, but this place is hopping like the clock just struck noon. Just like in the good old days, it’s cash only here, which you hand through the order window before picking up your meal at the other window. The choices are simple and don’t go far outside the hamburger, chicken, hot dog range. Tony’s most popular item has always been the deluxe beef burger with a hunk of cheese melted on top, and really the meal isn’t complete without a side of crinkle cut fries and a milkshake. Milkshakes come in chocolate, vanilla, strawberry, banana, pineapple and coffee, which can be mixed together to create whatever your little heart desires. Nostalgia never tasted so good. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Cash Only&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1/4 lb Cheeseburger, $5.48&lt;br&gt;
Vegetarian Burger, $5.39&lt;br&gt;
Grilled Chicken Breast Sandwich, $5.39&lt;br&gt;
All Beef Jumbo Chili Dog, $4.11&lt;br&gt;
Idaho Crinkle Cut French Fries, $2.42&lt;br&gt;
Thick Old Fashioned Milk Shake or Malt, $3.32&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Friday, 9 a.m. to 9:45 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday, 9:30 a.m. to 9:45 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, 9:30 a.m. to 8:45 p.m.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-10-28 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Tony's Cable Car Restaurant</location>
      <address>2500 Geary Blvd</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94115</zip>
      <latitude>37.7828</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.445</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 931-2416</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1563/original.jpg?1318878046</image>
      <website>http://www.tonyscablecar.com</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2536</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2536</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>This Isn’t Your Regular Ole Farmers Market, Folks</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2536/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1319649004" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Things you’re used to seeing at farmers markets: apples, lemons, flowers, maybe even some organic honey. Things you’re not used to seeing at farmers markets:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;iframe width="510" height="307" src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/8jivntGguLQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Video by &lt;a href="http://warholian.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Warholian&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

And that’s because this isn’t just a farmers market, it’s The Farmers Block, an “ecological pairing between art, music, and food, mostly local organic farms, and vegan/raw chefs, sometimes food trucks/carts” all wrapped up for your pleasure in one live event. This growing crew lives by “zenliness,” which is their term for when art, music, and food are paired properly in a sustainable, ecofriendly manner, and they want you to be a part of their collective:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: You sort of took the farmers market idea and injected some fun in to it. What was the inspiration?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
FARMERS BLOCK: My life and being in general. I've always cared about health and had a growing interest in holistics and dietary alternatives. Coming from that past, I think that's how I was subconsciously inspired. Consciously, I was inspired in many ways from thinking deeply about sustainability, networking, collaborating, trading and overall community. The places I shopped for produce and food, be it farmers markets, or major super markets, were not as uplifting as I thought they could be. I felt that a high level of passion was absent from the equation, although the exception is the &lt;a href="http://www.ferrybuildingmarketplace.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Ferry Building&lt;/a&gt; and Alemany Farmers Market, both of those being quite the distance for getting to and from. This all lead me to launching The Farmers Block. What was missing from the overall picture, to us, was a place to gather goods, sell, barter, or exchange the crafts, art, products of eco-friendly design, and healthier foods by way of connecting the friends that were within our existing circle.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: There are many different people involved in The Farmers Block (diggers, chefs, farmers, artists, musicians, filmmakers, &amp; entrepreneurs, probably just to name a few). What does a typical event look like?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
FARMERS BLOCK: We ideally bring out 20 artists, 20 fashion designers, 10/20 farms and chefs, also sustainable organizations and other grassroots collectives, pack the stages with beat producers/turntablists/emcees/musicians and top it off with visual art, like projections, and vj's. Everyone being local, and within the same community.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: You work at &lt;a href="http://treasureisland.jobcorps.gov/home.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;Treasure Island Job Corps&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/missions-kitchen-san-francisco" target="_blank"&gt;Mission Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;, to name a couple. What is it like to work in an environment with other people you’re not necessarily collaborating with?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
FARMERS BLOCK: It's great! If we’re cooking around others that aren't collaborating with us, we let them in on what TFB is doing and what foods/recipes we’re coming up with. Usually they are interested in helping or getting involved somehow after that. Food really brings people together no matter what.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;SCOUT: What’s the most important thing our Scouts should know about The Farmers Block?&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
FARMERS BLOCK: We want you be proactive and get involved with us! We’re completely grassroots, and not going to go the corporate route, we stay underground and for the people. Our collective is a brand, and coalition not just an event. If you’re an artist, musician, chef, farm, designer, activist, naturist, blogger, or creative in general, feel free to reach out to us! &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;And here’s where you can do that, and follow The Farmers Block to make sure you make it to their next event: &lt;a href="http://thefarmersblock.tumblr.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tumblr&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/THEFARMERSBLOCK" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/#!/thefarmersblock" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;@thefarmersblock&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2544</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2544</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Re-discovering Kaleidoscopic Fun</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2544/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1319648764" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The resident turnover in San Francisco seems to be just as consistent as the images in a kaleidoscope. That’s why we want to introduce you to (and remind some of you about) a public art installation on Octavia that’s been adding whimsy and mystery to the area since 2005. Wang Po Shu, through the &lt;a href="http://www.sfartscommission.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;San Francisco Arts Commission&lt;/a&gt;, installed 12 kaleidoscopes as part of his “Ghinlon/Transcope” piece. Their placement stretches from Octavia Boulevard and Market all the way to the Hayes Green.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

If you’ve never found yourself traipsing around this area, you probably had no idea they exist, but we can tell you these public kaleidoscopes are well worth the stop (just remember to always look both ways before crossing the street). Wang Po Shu used a unique mirror lens to allow viewers to take in the surrounding scene and put a new spin on it. The sculptures can swing 60 degrees up and down and 180 degrees from left to right, so if you get bored of an area, one little pivot provides a whole new world. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/Kaleidoscope.jpg" alt="Kaleidoscope Image" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Photo by Todd Lappin of &lt;a href="http://telstarlogistics.typepad.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Telstar Logistics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

We’re digging you kaleidoscopes, because sometimes, re-discovering is just as special as the initial discovery. </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1585</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1585</guid>
      <title>50% off The Blue Muse</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1585/original.jpg?1319219638" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; If you know anything about your Greek mythology, you know that the word &lt;i&gt;muse&lt;/i&gt; comes from the names for any of Zeus and Mnemosyne’s (ya, don’t even try) nine daughters who represented an art or science. The Blue Muse restaurant is in the middle of one of the city’s most artistic areas – it calls the Davies Symphony Hall, the War Memorial and Performing Arts Center, Bill Graham Auditorium and the San Francisco Ballet, neighbors. And the other part of the name? It just came to the restaurant’s owner “&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VonGs_aG_3A" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;out of the blue&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Most French restaurants come with white linen table cloths, duck entrées and a good wine selection, all things you’ll find at The Blue Muse, but this restaurant has something you won’t find at most other French restaurants: super friendly staff. None of that snooty, nose up in the air, if you don’t pronounce that impossible French word correctly I’m going to openly roll my eyes attitude. But even though the service is more casual, the food is still upscale and high quality. The mozzarella sticks aren’t something you’d ever find in a sports bar, these are mozzarella cheese stuffed with prosciutto and served with a side of tomato relish. Mains range from pastas to fish to chicken to duck (of course), all of which can be enjoyed alongside a specialty cocktail from the full bar. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Also, keep your eye on The Blue Muse’s &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/TheBlueMuse" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook page&lt;/a&gt; for upcoming events. The big concert venues aren’t the only ones putting a show on around here. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Golden Fried Brie Cheese, $8.95&lt;br&gt;
Cold Cucumber Soup, $6.95&lt;br&gt;
Shrimp Fussili, $16.95&lt;br&gt;
Breast of Chicken Provencale, $18.95&lt;br&gt;
Veal Sweetbread, $18.95&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Friday, 11 a.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday &amp; Sunday, 9:30 a.m. to 10 p.m.
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-10-27 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2012 02:59:59 -0500</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>The Blue Muse</location>
      <address>370 Grove St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94102</zip>
      <latitude>37.778</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.423</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 701-9888</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1585/original.jpg?1319219638</image>
      <website>http://www.facebook.com/TheBlueMuse</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2526</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2526</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Win A Prize If You Recognize</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2526/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1319567861" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;How well do you know your city? Give us your best guess on this mystery location and we'll send a sweet, sweet prize to one lucky winner.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Reply to the Scoutmob daily email with your answer, or hit us up through &lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/scoutmob" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://www.scoutmob.com/images/scoutmob_images/other_images/recognizedline.jpg"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2487/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1318956266"/&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


Last week’s answer: Cafe Flore&lt;br&gt;
Last week's winner: Eileen @ Ritual</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2526/SM_home_Contentimage2.jpg?1316545886</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2541</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2541</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Giving Twitter The Bird</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2541/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1319567741" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Would a Coca-Cola with any other logo taste as delicious? Would an Apple by any other name spark a worldwide frenzy any time a new product was released (ok, probably)? One of the most recognized logos in modern history (meaning since the beginning of the 2000’s) is Twitter’s blue bird. We like their design so much, when the fail whale pops up, we aren’t even that mad. But, what if Twitter had gone with another type of bird over the cheery little bluejay we’ve come to love? The website &lt;a href="http://www.designcontest.com/ugly-birds/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;designcontest.com re-imagined the logo&lt;/a&gt;, and came up with some that were cute and cuddly and others you might expect to pop up in a bad dream:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/aberthol512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Aberthol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/alwyn512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Alwyn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/amathaon512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Amathaon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/angor512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Angor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/avaon512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Avaon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/barris512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Barris&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/twitterbirds/bedwyr512.png" border="0" width="200" height="200" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Bedwyr&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

These designs are pretty rad, but don’t mess with what’s not broken, right?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1570</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1570</guid>
      <title>100% off Turtle Tower (SoMa)</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1570/original.jpg?1318974625" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Every time I hear the name of this restaurant, inevitably, the tune of that &lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Gn5iCn_T68c" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;popular late 80’s animated series featuring four of the toughest turtles ever&lt;/a&gt; goes jangling through my head. The turtles fought evil and the SoMa location of this Vietnamese restaurant is fighting hunger. The name Turtle Tower is synonymous with pho, which is what they’ll be dishing up for you for this deal, but don’t expect all the bean sprouts, basil and other accoutrements you’re used to seeing atop pho. Chef Steven Pham brings the simplicity and freshness of his native northern country recipes to San Francisco with pure broth and wide noodles cooked twice a day and flavorful, free range chicken. It may not be the chicken noodle soup your mom used to make, but the quality is superior and Chef Steven’s expertise is undeniable, and in a shared table setting, the company might be a tad livelier (don't tell your mom we said that).&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

No traditional Vietnamese meal is complete without some sort of roll as a starter. Choose produce-packed spring rolls stuffed with fresh shrimp and grilled pork, deep fried imperial rolls brimming with crab, shrimp, ground pork, black fungus, silver noodle and more, or the newest addition to the menu, the texture-iffic banh cuon, steamed rice sheets stuffed with ground pork. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

Turtle Tower recently added a dinner menu available only at the SoMa location; which is just down the street when you think about the fact you’d have to go all the way to Vietnam to get it otherwise. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Phở Gà (Chicken Noodle Soup, small), $6.20&lt;br&gt;
Gỏi Cuốn (Spring Rolls), $5.15&lt;br&gt;
Nem Cua (Imperial Rolls), 2.15 (each)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;From the Dinner Menu:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Vit Ham – pressure cooked duck, $14.95&lt;br&gt;
Mì xào hải sản – egg noodle with assorted seafood, $12.95&lt;br&gt;
Rau Xao/Luoc – mixed vegetables, $12.95&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Saturday, 10 a.m. to 9 p.m.
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-10-26 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>100%</percentageOff>
      <location>Turtle Tower (SoMa)</location>
      <address>501 6th St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94103</zip>
      <latitude>37.776</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.402</longitude>
      <phone>415-904-9888</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1570/original.jpg?1318974625</image>
      <website>http://www.facebook.com/pages/Turtle-Tower/228546690432</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2522</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2522</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Time Out For Winey Adults</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2522/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1319484470" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;We're lucky to live smack dab in the middle of one of our nation's biggest wine supplying areas. That means the good stuff floweth like water around here, albeit at a slightly higher cost. And when the mood strikes you to reach for the red, white or bubbly, you've got plenty of options. Last week we asked you: &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WHERE DO YOU GO WHEN YOU'RE FEELING WINEY?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR SCOUT SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;a href="http://www.quesyrahsf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Que Syrah&lt;/a&gt; is one wine bar I am willing to go out of my way to get to. Not only do I love the witty name (in Spanish, que sera means &lt;i&gt;whatever will be&lt;/i&gt;), but the chef also cooks up the most scrumptious dishes for pairings, like the upcoming Pork Rib Paella and Iberian Wine Tasting on November 12th. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;YOU SAYS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.hotelbiron.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Hotel Biron&lt;/a&gt;"&lt;br&gt;
- Jessica Barry&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"‎&lt;a href="http://www.delluvasf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Dell'Uva&lt;/a&gt; in North Beach. HUGE selection of wine, super knowledgeable staff, they have amazing food and best of all, it's not snobby. It's the type of wine bar that you go to and watch the game on TV. The music is usually something fun and upbeat. And they have plenty of sidewalk seating, perfect for those amazing nights that we've been having. Whenever I'm feeling the need for some wine and good company, I'll head over to Dell'Uva and without fail, have an awesome experience. Every time. :)"&lt;br&gt;
- Katt Katsumi&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.thegoodhotel.com/sidebar" target="_blank"&gt;Side Bar&lt;/a&gt; by the Good Hotel on 7th is newly remodeled and has very reasonable prices!"&lt;br&gt;
- Joshua Lim&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.pressclubsf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Press Club&lt;/a&gt; - only if you want the best!"&lt;br&gt;
- Jai Singh&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.yieldsf.com/YieldWineBar/Welcome.html" target="_blank"&gt;Yield Wine Bar&lt;/a&gt; in the Dogpatch hood and &lt;a href="http://www.internoswinecafe.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Internos Wine Bar&lt;/a&gt; near USF."&lt;br&gt;
- Rita Chretien&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.heartsf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Heart&lt;/a&gt;"&lt;br&gt;
- Shelley Gladwin Estelle&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"&lt;a href="http://www.terroirsf.com/" target="_blank"&gt;TERROIR&lt;/a&gt;!"&lt;br&gt;
- Kyra Brown&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;



&lt;strong&gt;NEXT WEEK’S WHAT SAY YOU: &lt;/strong&gt;The holidays are coming. That means lots of parties, and lots of fancy outfits you're going to have to wear to make sure you look your best. Which store do you depend on to hook you up with the coolest duds? Hit us up on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2522/SM_home_Contentimage2.jpg?1318281131</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2534</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2534</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>D.I. Why Don’t You Do It Yourself?</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sf_bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2534/SF_bigthumb2.jpg?1319487370" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;“I wanna do it!” This phrase is usually heard coming from the mouth of a bratty toddler, but thanks to all the DIY spots in the city, you can now utter it and sound confident, not whiny. We put together a list of the best spots to get your hands dirty and make something that’ll have mom bragging to all her friends:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://techshop.ws/tssf.html" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;TechShop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
“What do &lt;i&gt;you&lt;/i&gt; want to make?” With over &lt;a href="http://techshop.ws/take_classes.html?storeId=4" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;90 classes scheduled&lt;/a&gt; and open hours from 9 a.m. to midnight, TechShop will teach you everything from making stained glass masterpieces to how to weld steel and aluminum. Even though you can learn how to turn a sweater in to a pencil skirt here, the focus is more hardware than sewing store.&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/techschop.jpg" border="0" alt="Tech Shop Logo" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr style="color:#d0d0c2;background-color:#d0d0c2;height:1px;border:none; margin-top:-5px;" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class="article_description"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.workshopsf.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Workshop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
If you’ve never been to one of Kelly Malone’s productions, you might not be a local. Whether &lt;a href="http://www.workshopsf.org/?page_id=140&amp;id=859" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;learning how to make wine from a kit&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://www.workshopsf.org/?page_id=140&amp;id=888&amp;date=2011-11-08" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;mastering smokey eyes and nude lips&lt;/a&gt; or supporting local artists at &lt;a href="http://www.indie-mart.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Indie Mart&lt;/a&gt;, Workshop lets you unleash your creative power all under the careful guidance of a trained professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/workshop.jpg" border="0" alt="Workshop Logo" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr style="color:#d0d0c2;background-color:#d0d0c2;height:1px;border:none; margin-top:-5px;" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class="article_description"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.skillshare.com/learn" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Skillshare&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Skillshare encourages you to go both ways. Not like that! At Skillshare, you can “learn anything from anyone,” thanks to a sharing of skills (ah, now it’s all coming together). We &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2423" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Culture Hunted&lt;/a&gt; it a few weeks ago and can’t wait to make our very own sock money friend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/skillshare.jpg" border="0" alt="Skillshare Logo" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr style="color:#d0d0c2;background-color:#d0d0c2;height:1px;border:none; margin-top:-5px;" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class="article_description"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.bikekitchen.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;The Bike Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
We haven’t seen official numbers on how many cyclists live in SF, but the &lt;a href="http://www.sfbike.org/?about" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;San Francisco Bike Coalition&lt;/a&gt; has 12,000 members and counting, so we’re going to guess a lot. The Bike Kitchen is where bike enthusiasts go to give their wheels a tune-up, or even build the darn thing from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com.s3.amazonaws.com/others/bickkitchen.jpg" border="0" alt="Bike Kitchen Logo" /&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;hr style="color:#d0d0c2;background-color:#d0d0c2;height:1px;border:none; margin-top:-5px;" /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;p class="article_description"&gt;Any other gems out there we missed? Let us know about your favorite DIY spot on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2479</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2479</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Baller Meatballs </title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2479/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage2.jpg?1319235258" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Meatballs. Balls of meat. Doesn’t sound super appetizing when you break it down like that, but we all know these Italian goodies come second only to pizza. &lt;a href="http://missionfruition.com" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Mission Fruition’s Carina Ost&lt;/a&gt; knows a thing or two about these meat-packed spheres, and says she’s so fond of them, she’d even take a page from &lt;i&gt;The Wedding Singer&lt;/i&gt; and let little old ladies pay her in meatballs.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

There is an Italian, with East Coast/Jewish influences, gourmet-to-go spot near my house called &lt;a href="http://www.yelp.com/biz/pasta-gina-san-francisco" target="_blank"&gt;Pasta Gina&lt;/a&gt;, I just call it Dammmmn, Gina that serves up some delicious balls and is my regular go to joint. But when we are talking sit down restaurant and a serious meatball no one makes a bigger, better ball than &lt;a href="http://www.tonyspizzanapoletana.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Tony’s Pizza Napoletana&lt;/a&gt;. You must, I repeat, must order a Meatball Gigante with Sea Salted Burrata ($13). The meatball is absolutely enormous with burrata on top. It is such a major meatball that it definitely wouldn’t fall off the table with a sneeze, unless maybe it was done by a giant.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

I get a bit baffled about how something so large can be so evenly and perfectly cooked but I don’t worry much as I am too busy sticking my knife and fork into this monstrosity. It is the size of a softball or a grapefruit and each piece of the ball gets re-dunked in the sauce for extra coating and then forked with fresh burrata and ribbons of basil. This dish is truly a victory and is a great starter for those who won’t or can’t be satisfied with just pizza alone. The meatball gigante also comes in more fun options like wild mushroom, pancetta, and robiola or with a farm egg and calabrese but for me I like the cheese, please.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;Meatballs aren’t the only thing on Carina’s list when it comes to Tony’s Pizza Napoletana. &lt;a href="http://missionfruition.com/2011/10/17/hey-tony-thats-a-good-meatball/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Find out what other dish she says she will not go without&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1574</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1574</guid>
      <title>50% off 31 RAX</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1574/original.jpg?1319072704" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; Two weeks was all it took for Stephanie Madrinan to get her store, 31 RAX &lt;a href="http://3.bp.blogspot.com/-hr5MzyMhFRQ/TipEl6o4U_I/AAAAAAAABU0/uRTS6f0-vWk/s1600/yao-ming-running-backwards-training-nba-funny-photos.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;up and running&lt;/a&gt;. This airy, vaulted-ceiling space use to house a gym, so when she moved in, Stephanie made use of the metal scraps, lockers and other materials the previous owners left behind to erect dressing rooms and clothing racks. Building her store out of recycled materials just made sense since that’s the basis of what she sells here: vintage-thrift clothing she hand-picks during bi-monthly trips to one of the nation’s biggest fashion capitals: L.A. Even though the clothes are from down south, the styles Stephanie chooses would look good walking down Valencia for a cup of coffee or waiting in a brunch line in Hayes Valley. While the pieces are quintessentially SF-thrift, the store and prices are not. In fact, the organization and cleanliness of the store and clothing has caused some passersby to peer in and comment “Hm, looks expensive.” But with dresses going for $15 and all guy’s t-shirts priced at $9, you could easily pull together a try-on pile without checking one price tag. When’s the last time you did that?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

31 RAX just opened its doors last month, but keep an eye on &lt;a href="http://31rax.tumblr.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;the store’s site&lt;/a&gt; for upcoming event announcements. Stephanie’s already hosted speed dating (two attendees are now dating!) and bingo and has a whole list of fun ideas up her her fashionable sleeves. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Boutique Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Skirts, $12 – $15&lt;br&gt;
Dresses, $15 – $18&lt;br&gt;
Guy’s T-shirts, $9&lt;br&gt;
Flannels, $15&lt;br&gt;
Vests, $10 – $12&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday, 1 p.m. to 8 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Tuesday – Saturday, noon to 8 p.m.&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, Closed</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-10-25 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2012 23:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>31 RAX</location>
      <address>3309 Mission St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94110</zip>
      <latitude>37.744</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.421</longitude>
      <phone>415-617-5602</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1574/original.jpg?1319072704</image>
      <website>http://31rax.tumblr.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2518</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2518</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do on the Weeknights, October 24-27</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2518/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1319235039" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;'Twas the week before Halloween and all through the city, people readied their costumes: Angry Birds, Charlie Sheen and sexy kitty. Ok, actually, we hope you all are planning something a little more original than that. And, since official Halloween falls on a school night, you can wear your costume all weekend, non-stop and no one has the right to give you any guff about it. Don’t worry, even if you're wearing a cape, you'll fit in perfectly here:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

SPOOKY ART OPENING AT PUBLIC WORKS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Thursday, October 27, 6 p.m. to 10 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
“Nights of Darkness” takes over Roll Up Gallery this Thursday, but they’ll leave the lights on so you can see the spooky art that will be bringing a little black to the white walls. Seven artists will be sharing their sinister art at this free event.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=277707522251903" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;More Info&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1502" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;HANGR 16 Boutique&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

THE MAKING OF THE BAY LIGHTS&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Wednesday, October 26, 5:30 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The Bay Bridge is going to be just a tad brighter come this time next year when Ben Davis’ ginormous art installation (seven times the scale of the Eiffel Tower) is installed. $20 gets you beer, wine, appetizers and probably a lot of jaw dropping once you hear Ben’s stories. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://chromiumforum2.eventbrite.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets are $20&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1266" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Bar Basic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

RAW: Fashion + Music + Art&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Thursday, October 27, 7:30 p.m. to Midnight&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Whoever said San Francisco doesn’t know how to dress has obviously never attended a RAW event. It’s a fashion show set to a jivin’ DJ, featuring only the work of local artists. &lt;a href="http://www.rawartists.org/sanfrancisco/pulse" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets are $10&lt;/a&gt;, and remember to iron your finest duds, this is a cocktail attire event. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.facebook.com/event.php?eid=129519763815193" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;More details&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1570" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Turtle Tower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1548</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1548</guid>
      <title>50% off Hobson's Choice Bar</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Original" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1548/original.jpg?1318791318" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Scoop:&lt;/strong&gt; A Hobson’s Choice is thinking you have options, when you really only have one. The term dates way back to an English stable owner who, in order to rotate the use of his horses, would offer riders the horse in the stall near the door, or nothing at all. At Victorian punch house Hobson’s Choice, in the Haight, there a ton of drink options on the menu, including a gargantuan shareable punch bowl that could quench a horse’s thirst (&lt;a href="http://www.chorvaloo.com/content/wp-content/uploads/2010/02/tired-horse.jpg" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;and get him really wasted&lt;/a&gt;). But even though it might seem like Hobson’s Choice is offering you a bevy of beverage options, they’ve slyly provided you with one main choice, no matter what you select, and that’s guaranteed lip smacking, rum-based cocktails. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Scout Notes:&lt;/strong&gt; The sign on the window says “Victorian,” but one foot through the door and you’ll get a sense of the general theme on your own. The red chairs and small, round wooden tables (about the size of a punch bowl, you might say) give Hobson’s Choice an old timey, parlory, saloon feel, almost to the point that you expect to see a boa-wrapped lady of the evening posted up near a piano that’s cranking out some Charlie Chaplin-esque music. The cocktail list here has an undeniable tropical vibe thanks to ingredients like Cruzan coconut and banana rums, pineapple and lime juice and blue Curaçao. Drinks like the Barbados Punch, made with Bacardi spiced rum, Cruzan orange rum, lime and pineapple juice and Cruzan pineapple rum and the June Bug, Midori, Cruzan coconut and banana rums, pineapple juice and sweet and sour are a nice taste of what Hobson’s has to offer, but when else can you get a Prom-worthy punch bowl filled with your choice of three different kinds of punch? Yes, people, the punch bowls are where it’s at. Ladies and gentlemen, your choices are: Victorian Punch – silver, coconut and pineapple rums, cranberry and pineapple juice. GoGo Punch – raspberry, citrus and silver rums, organic lemonade, pineapple juice and a splash of ginger. House Punch – silver rum, mango, orange and pineapple juice. See? Sometimes having one choice is a good thing, especially when it comes to trying to pick between scrumptious bowls of booze. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;HR&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Menu Highlights:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Drinks:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Pineapple Upside-Down Cake – Cruzan pineapple &amp; vanilla rums, lime &amp; pineapple juice, $7.50&lt;br&gt;
Bahama Mama – Cruzan banana &amp; coconut rums, Kahlua, pineapple juice, sweet &amp; sour, $7.50&lt;br&gt;
Zombie – Cruzan light rum, Brugal gold rum, Whaler’s dark rum, lemon &amp; pineapple juice, $8&lt;br&gt;
Dark &amp; Stormy – Gosling’s black seal rum &amp; ginger beer, $6.50&lt;br&gt;
House Punch Bowl, $30&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;Hours:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Monday – Friday, 1 p.m. - 2 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
Saturday, noon to 2 a.m.&lt;br&gt;
Sunday, 10 a.m. - 2 a.m.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <siteEndDate>2011-10-24 02:59:59</siteEndDate>
      <expirationDate>Sat, 21 Apr 2012 02:59:59 -0400</expirationDate>
      <percentageOff>50%</percentageOff>
      <location>Hobson's Choice Bar</location>
      <address>1601 Haight St</address>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <state>CA</state>
      <zip>94117</zip>
      <latitude>37.7697</latitude>
      <longitude>-122.449</longitude>
      <phone>(415) 621-5859</phone>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/deals/1548/original.jpg?1318791318</image>
      <website>http://www.hobsonschoice.com/</website>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2491</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2491</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>Caption This! Friday Photo Fun</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Bigthumb2" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2491/BigThumb2.jpg?1319125581" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Give us your best witty caption to go with this extra curious pic on &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/scoutmobsf" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="
http://www.facebook.com/ScoutmobSF" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt; 

We'll post some our favorites to this here website.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

As for this interesting image from last week, here are some of the caption contributions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;img src=" http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/seen/2453/captionthis.jpg?1318426020"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;OUR FAVORITE:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Before Charles Manson's days as an infamous cult leader, he spent a summer abroad doing charcoal portraits of tourists. It was less successful than he had hoped. This made him sad."&lt;br&gt;
- Elissa Cain

&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;HONORABLE MENTIONS:&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"I said, have you seen my red balloon, you hairy chump!"&lt;br&gt;
- George Georgerson&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"The late delivery of pencils had now created a backlog in the Albanian passport office's picture dept."&lt;br&gt;
- Bill Ford&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"You want "broke-down baby doll" Tyra? I'll give you that and some fierce eyes. mmmkay"&lt;br&gt;
- Dallas Howell&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Derek began working on "Blue Steel" at a very early age."&lt;br&gt;
- Todd Wilson&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Yeah, Well you'd be lookin angry too if your mother made you dress like this."&lt;br&gt;
- Joe Bach&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Years later, little Bobby would sell his portrait by the shoe bomber on eBay for enough money for therapy lessons he so dearly needed."&lt;br&gt;
- Andrew Dodd&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Be sure to get the open toed shoes and tick socks combination... that's the reason why I'm here!"&lt;br&gt;
- Leah Wells&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

"Not exactly the Kate-and-Leo moment young Terrence was hoping for."&lt;br&gt;
- Katie Brinkworth</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/today/2491/BW2.jpg?1316724954</image>
    </item>
    <item>
      <link>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2510</link>
      <guid>http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/scoutfinds/2510</guid>
      <city>San Francisco</city>
      <title>What to Do This Weekend, October 21-23</title>
      <description>&lt;img alt="Sm_scoutfinds_mainimage1" src="http://cloud.scoutmob.com/upload/images/articles/scoutfind/original/2510/SM_Scoutfinds_Mainimage1.jpg?1319126115" /&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Historical zombies grape stomping. That’s what you’d get if you combined all of this weekend’s can’t-miss-em events. Sounds a little scary, but we’ve probably seen worse just walking around the city. This weekend, it’s all about getting outside, with the occasional stop off at the bar, of course:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;WE DON’T WANT TO MISS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

ZOMBIE PUB CRAWL&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday, October 22, 7 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Sometimes, after a hard night of drinking, we feel like death. Start the night out that way during the Zombie Pub Crawl. Make sure to come dressed in torn, blood spattered clothing, otherwise someone may try to bite you. Three stops are scheduled, but when you’re a zombie, you’ve got all the time in the world, to party hardy for as long as you feel like it.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://sfzombiecrawl.blogspot.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Zombie Pub Crawl&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;100% OFF! DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1501" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Bob’s Donut and Pastry Shop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;


&lt;strong&gt;ALSO WORTH CHECKING OUT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

BARBARY COAST TRAIL WALK&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Sunday, October 23, 9 a.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
“Your favorite city, right at your feet.” Explore some of San Francisco’s most historical spots on this 3.5 mile walk from the Old Mint to Aquatic Park. Guides in costumes will lead the way, pointing out the areas you should pay special attention to... there may be a pop quiz later. The walk ends at the Maritime National Historical Park with a party that will be one for the history books. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://barbarycoasttrailwalk.org/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Barbary Coast Trail Walk&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1530" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;La Canasta&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

GRAPE STOMPING BASH AT THE WINERY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;Saturday, October 22, noon to 5 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Come Saturday, you could be squishing through a barrel of grapes if you play your cards right and have $45 to spend. In addition to stomping the crap out of some fruit, you’ll also get to taste new wines from &lt;a href="http://winery-sf.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;The Winery&lt;/a&gt; and get a chance to win wine and barrel sampling for 10 people.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://grapestompingbash.eventbrite.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Tickets are $45&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1398" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Fuzio Universal Bistro&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;i&gt;BONUS EVENT!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
POSTAGRAM + SCOUTMOB: THE 1197 AFTER-PARTY&lt;br&gt;
&lt;i&gt;October 22, 6:30 p.m. to 9 p.m.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;
1197 is a one day mobile photo conference, but we’re gonna keep this party going allllllll night. Or at least until 9. We’re teaming up with Postagram for an after party at 111 Minna where you will enjoy food from the dynamic duo at &lt;a href="http://www.ricepaperscissors.com/" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;Rice Paper Scissors&lt;/a&gt;, drinks, dancing and new prints by four very talented Twitterers. Free entry and open to everyone!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="http://blog.postagramapp.com/postagram-and-scoutmob-present-the-1197-after" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;More details&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

&lt;strong&gt;DEAL NEARBY ON THE APP: &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="http://scoutmob.com/san-francisco/deal/1566" style="color:#d66c2a;" target="_blank"&gt;L’acajou Bakery and Café&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 03:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <image>/images/default_today_pic.jpg</image>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
